[{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5226"},"answer":"Search the y-axis for the desired start time. In this case, it is 12pm. Then trace the line stemming from the mark at 12pm that angles to the right until a point is reached to find the event starting at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84435,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV","time_elapsed":541204,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf523e"},"answer":"Look on the horizontal axis and go vertical ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":22502,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ","time_elapsed":573245,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5256"},"answer":"Find 12 PM on the horizontal line and go straight up to see if there are any points that indicate events that start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45457,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5","time_elapsed":744947,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf526e"},"answer":"Shifts F and B start. Shift J ends, Shift I and J ends. Shift E is still going on.\n\nLook to the left of 12 to see what shifts are still occurring/ending, and also look at 12 to see what shifts are starting.  ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61038,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL","time_elapsed":627701,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5286"},"answer":"Go on the bottom, find 12pm and look to see which letters fall on that line vertically. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30325,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT","time_elapsed":818369,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf529e"},"answer":"To determine what events start at 12pm, locate the 12pm time at the base of the pyramid and observe which letters are dotted along the right horizontal line coming from \"12pm\"","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":78182,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB","time_elapsed":862324,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b6"},"answer":"you look where it says 12 pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":49707,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4","time_elapsed":673611,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ce"},"answer":"I look at the x-axis which is the bottom axis who's title is start & end time. I look at the x-axis, i find 12pm on it and that helps me determine what starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43185,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05","time_elapsed":763525,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e6"},"answer":"you look at the x axis, find 12pm, and movce up from there to see if either a shift starts,ends, etc.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47379,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB","time_elapsed":782937,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52fe"},"answer":"x axis 12 PM, so F & B","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":21385,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP","time_elapsed":533284,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5316"},"answer":"To determine the events that start at 12 pm, you must first locate 12 pm on the x-axis. Once you find the location of 12 pm on the x-axis, follow the line with the positive slope that stems out from the 12 pm mark. Every shift that is along that line will start at 12 pm. In this case, shifts M and L are found on that line, meaning that they will both start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":178074,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6","time_elapsed":717646,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf532e"},"answer":"Any dot that the diagonal line with positive/increasing slope beginning at 12pm passes through","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":155007,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4","time_elapsed":1288053,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5346"},"answer":"Compare the various start times to see who's breaks overlap and who starts work and who is finished up for the day.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29520,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH","time_elapsed":1163882,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf535e"},"answer":"By looking at the X-axis and seeing the points that fall under the 12pm category.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42610,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM","time_elapsed":931213,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5376"},"answer":"look at the x axis, find 12 AND THEN GO UP THE Y AXIS FROM THAT POINT AND NOTE ALL THE SHADED DOTS","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115-late","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43125,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8","time_elapsed":582961,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf538e"},"answer":"To figure out what events start at 12 pm, you trace the start time of 12pm to the duration in hours.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35620,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR","time_elapsed":603455,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a6"},"answer":"Looking at the X-axis, find 12 pm and go straight up to see which events/shifts begin at that time","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41045,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU","time_elapsed":586108,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d6"},"answer":"I look at the points on the 12 pm y axis and then look at other points to see if events ending later could possibly start at 12 pm by subtracting hours\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53121,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC","time_elapsed":849580,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ee"},"answer":"i personally find 12pm on the x-axis and drag my finger upward. whichever shift overlaps i note down.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52087,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2","time_elapsed":807411,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5406"},"answer":"I look at the start time of the day ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29801,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW","time_elapsed":673706,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf541e"},"answer":"Go to the 12pm marker at bottom then follow it up the cross section to see the dots that fall onto the time ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41447,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3","time_elapsed":780725,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5436"},"answer":"check the x axis and see what points lie on the 12pm \n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32990,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8","time_elapsed":750249,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf544e"},"answer":"look for 12 pm on the x axis and see what letters are on the graph when x = 12 pm ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34266,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092","time_elapsed":884744,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5466"},"answer":"if you look at the horizontal axis and look at the 12pm mark you can see which shifts start at 12pm by seeing which dot matches up to that mark vertically.\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115-late","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":110162,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX","time_elapsed":809510,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf547e"},"answer":"look at 12pm and what is above are the events start at 12pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36420,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT","time_elapsed":737124,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5496"},"answer":"For the lines going right slanting right, the events that start at 12 PM will begin at 12 PM on the x-axis and then move upwards, like with the letters M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":39185,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY","time_elapsed":724679,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ae"},"answer":"Look at which events are on the y axis corresponds to the 12pm x axis value.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45866,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U","time_elapsed":521721,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c6"},"answer":"I SEE WHICH POINTS HAVE 12 PM AS THEIR X COORDINATE\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32382,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0","time_elapsed":495070,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54de"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis and fine where it says 12pm. When located, all the values in that column start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35627,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L","time_elapsed":725424,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f6"},"answer":"Look for data points along the y-axis that align with 12 PM on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":70704,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC","time_elapsed":619638,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf550e"},"answer":"Beginning of F and B's shift.\nEnd of J's shift. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42711,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW","time_elapsed":660783,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5526"},"answer":"To determine which events start at 12pm, follow the line leaning towards the right starting at 12pm on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":69332,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98","time_elapsed":669422,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf553e"},"answer":"go towards the bottom of chart find 12pm and look any dot on 12pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":70266,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7","time_elapsed":690672,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5556"},"answer":"The x axis says that shifts for b and f start","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41088,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU","time_elapsed":736330,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf556e"},"answer":"An event starts at 12pm when there is a point above the number 12 on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":155952,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE","time_elapsed":2133615,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5586"},"answer":"Look at the x axis of start and end times. Go to 12PM and look straight up that line for the letter of the shift","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45760,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B","time_elapsed":1252124,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf559e"},"answer":"FOLLOW THE / LINE STARTING AT 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30845,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK","time_elapsed":417899,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b6"},"answer":"Looking at the x - axis ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66944,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP","time_elapsed":844139,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ce"},"answer":"you go to 12 pm on the x-axis and then go directly vertical from that position. Whatever points fall on that line start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55070,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW","time_elapsed":783022,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e6"},"answer":"You look at the x-axis and find the point on it labeled \"12pm\". Then, you look at all the points on the graph that are directly above that 12pm label. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":57753,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96","time_elapsed":787309,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55fe"},"answer":"Find the 12PM mark on the x axis and then move directly up to find the dots that are right above this point.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51142,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3","time_elapsed":896998,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5616"},"answer":"You go to the x axis and look for where it says 12 pm, then you go up the y axis from the starting point of 12 pm and see which dots fall in that line going up.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":70550,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD","time_elapsed":1292813,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf562e"},"answer":"X-Axis represents time of day. The dots represent the start of the shift.\nSo only the X-axis matters in finding 12pm start.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84864,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3","time_elapsed":1323346,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5646"},"answer":"Follow the line going diagonally up/right from the 12pm. Any point that passes through this line is an event that begins at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":62464,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M","time_elapsed":731399,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf565e"},"answer":"First indicate the 12pm slot on the x-axis and trace the right-most diagonal connected to this slot up until you find points of intersection. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47921,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB","time_elapsed":2242091,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5676"},"answer":"The events that start at 12 PM will fall on a straight, upward line protruding from the 12 PM spot on the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":74211,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4","time_elapsed":772952,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf568e"},"answer":"Follow the diagonal line up from the 12pm slot","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":15949,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2","time_elapsed":1222396,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a6"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis(which is for start & end times), and then follow the time up vertically to see which letters start at a given time. In this case, B and F start at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":86637,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3","time_elapsed":1216969,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d6"},"answer":"LOOK AT THE X-AXIS FOR 12 pm AND GO UP THE GRAPH","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30693,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P","time_elapsed":982198,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ee"},"answer":"any dots that are placed before 12pm ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35646,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ","time_elapsed":631069,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5706"},"answer":"First find 12pm on the x-axis and then go up from the 12pm point and find any dots that represent events. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":145011,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R","time_elapsed":731703,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5736"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis (start and end time) and then look up the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25947,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU","time_elapsed":991689,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf574e"},"answer":"shifts on the line that start at 12 and goes upper right direction","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":124841,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0","time_elapsed":659815,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5766"},"answer":"There are two diagonal lines leading away from 12PM. The one towards the left means any events ending at 12pm, and one towards the right is any events starting at 12pm. You can follow the right line to see that M and L both start at 12pm, since they are both on this line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":132503,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD","time_elapsed":708237,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf577e"},"answer":"F and B begin there shift.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37057,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP","time_elapsed":552439,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5796"},"answer":"you look at the time on the bottom and then look at what dots are on that line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":21600,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD","time_elapsed":726315,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ae"},"answer":"I look at the x-axis for \"START & END TIME (time of day)\" and search for 12PM. Then I scan vertically up to see which shift(s) is/are directly on that 12 PM line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":105686,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL","time_elapsed":885467,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c6"},"answer":"Find the point of 12 PM at x axis, and the line that begins at this point and positive ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":130506,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS","time_elapsed":768554,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57de"},"answer":"lOOK AT THE X-AXIS FOR 12 PM AND SEE THE DOTS THAT MATCH UP WITH IT.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":20801,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T","time_elapsed":654089,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f6"},"answer":"Read the x axis, indicated start and end time. Upon reaching the 12 pm marker, read vertically upward. The dots that fall on this line are those starting at 12 pm. They end at a time indicated by the y axis, which reads duration (in hours).","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":121326,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF","time_elapsed":725627,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf580e"},"answer":"find 12pm on the x axis and see which plot points are above it","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35578,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD","time_elapsed":637627,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5826"},"answer":"look up 12 on the x axis and then follow from that point up the y axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":64487,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ","time_elapsed":864473,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf583e"},"answer":"Any event that is on a positive sloped line intersecting 12pm or any event whose x-coordinate shifted to the left by their (y-coordinate divided by 2) is 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":157147,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z","time_elapsed":760792,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5856"},"answer":"Start at 12 PM on the horizontal axis, and then follow the line angled toward the right. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61980,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA","time_elapsed":852278,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf586e"},"answer":"Start at 12 from the bottom of the graph (x-axis) and follow the line that goes up and towards the right.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59183,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE","time_elapsed":860194,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5886"},"answer":"By looking at the X axis of the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25359,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ","time_elapsed":913338,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf589e"},"answer":"Follow the lines coming from 12 and get M and L. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":21527,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9","time_elapsed":414034,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b6"},"answer":"Go up, then choose the points that above twelve pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":88423,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS","time_elapsed":1538876,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ce"},"answer":"Look at where 12 pm is and the events lined up along that vertical axis start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":45557,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG","time_elapsed":838729,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e6"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis and then look at the point; the x-coordinate of the point. For example, look at 12 pm on the x-axis and then follow it straight up and once you reach the points those points start at 12 pm. So for 12 pm it would be shifts B and F.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":89710,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A","time_elapsed":804068,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58fe"},"answer":"I would look along the x- axis until i see 12pm. Then I look up the y-axis to see which shift would begin at that time.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":57212,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6","time_elapsed":1330634,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5916"},"answer":"You determine what events start at 12 pm by looking at whether there is a black dot there, which signifies that someone started a shift at that time, or you trace the duration of hours along with the black dots at different hours to see if someone is supposed to have a break there.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":132808,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ","time_elapsed":1026446,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf592e"},"answer":"took me a few questions to figure out, but the left corner of the equilateral triangle (positioning the letter at the top) is where the time starts and the right corner is where the time ends. So I figure out what triangles' lower corner is positioned at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":87280,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ","time_elapsed":552600,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5946"},"answer":"An event's start time is shown by the diagonal connection down to the left side at the data point 12PM on the time of day axis.  ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58525,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61","time_elapsed":989894,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf595e"},"answer":"look at the x axis until you hit 12pm and then look up at the dots that lie on it","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":44715,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6","time_elapsed":615605,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5976"},"answer":"on the x axis go to 12 pm and move upwards until reaching a letter indicating an event that is happening at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30031,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR","time_elapsed":856325,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf598e"},"answer":"Must in the line for 12 and Duration less than four","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47573,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA","time_elapsed":888431,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59be"},"answer":"The left side of the line hits the 12 Pm point on the x axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":18938,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27","time_elapsed":360666,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d6"},"answer":"By looking at the x axis and seeing which point coincides with the time 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"111","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53285,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F","time_elapsed":1072340,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ee"},"answer":"You go to 12 p.m. on the x-axis, and then follow the right diagonal line until you see a letter(shift). In this case, it'd be M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75306,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT","time_elapsed":551093,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a06"},"answer":"The black dots indicate the start time\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34230,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2","time_elapsed":1075899,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a1e"},"answer":"you start at twelve then follow the right slanted line to M and L all the way up the pyramid\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":42708,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4","time_elapsed":1142115,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a36"},"answer":"Which ever shift is diagonally connected to the 12pm on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":38460,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG","time_elapsed":670274,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a4e"},"answer":"I use the mouse to line up where a letter and the time meet on the graph","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60206,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD","time_elapsed":727046,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a66"},"answer":"Tracing the line from 12 pm on the x-axis vertically up to notice B and F\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26371,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK","time_elapsed":670341,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a7e"},"answer":"You find 12pm on the x-axis and then you see if there are any points that are directly above the 12pm increment to see if any shifts start then. To find out when a break is taking place at 12pm you test one's shift by dividing their duration by 2 and adding that to when they started their shift. If the answer is 12 pm then thats when their break is.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":139339,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08","time_elapsed":902533,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aae"},"answer":"The lines that come out of 12 pm going to right and up is lines that have a shift start. \nLines going up and to the left are shift ends. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":50123,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH","time_elapsed":630380,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac6"},"answer":"Events that start at 12p.m are indicated by the black dots, which symbolize beginning time. Simply locate the black dot that is vertical to the time \"12 PM.\" ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53098,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0","time_elapsed":924413,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ade"},"answer":"Look at the x axis, and go to the 12pm data value. Then, find the valid corresponding durations for events that start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68922,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2","time_elapsed":847520,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af6"},"answer":"look at the vertical line going up from 12 pm mark on the horizontal axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":30869,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M","time_elapsed":666165,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b0e"},"answer":"Look at the points corresponding to 12 pm from the x-axis.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33165,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09","time_elapsed":543710,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b26"},"answer":"From each shift (dot), you look at the triangle that forms under it. The first left line of the triangle tells you the shift start time and the right line of the triangle stemming from the dot tells you the shift end time. So to determine which shifts start at 12pm, you look at the diagonal lines that slant towards the right from the 12 pm tick mark on the graph, indicating the start time. You can follow the right-slanting diagonal line all the way through to see that shifts M and L start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":144307,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ","time_elapsed":986945,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b3e"},"answer":"First find the point of 12PM on x-axis, then trace the line towards the up-right direction of the 12PM point;the points lie on the line are the events we are looking for, which is M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":123812,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L","time_elapsed":924178,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b56"},"answer":"i was looking vertically up from 12 pm but idk what the hell im doing ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40528,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A","time_elapsed":461797,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b6e"},"answer":"I looked at which parts hard a circle lining up vertically from the 12 o'clock point on the x-axis. I had used the axis to help determine that the beginning times were the dots.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61160,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB","time_elapsed":1054486,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b86"},"answer":"To determine what events start at 12pm you would look at the X-axis labeled start and end time.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":23146,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH","time_elapsed":517401,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb6"},"answer":"Look at the X-axis and find which points line up vertically with 12 PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52181,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW","time_elapsed":773497,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bce"},"answer":"find the line going out from point 12PM on the x axis and find points on that path.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":74344,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY","time_elapsed":764864,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be6"},"answer":"Go to the 12pm mark on the x-axis, and move along the corresponding grid line that points to the upper right corner. Any events that intercept this line start at 12pm. In this case, it would be M and L. I didn't figure this out until halfway through.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":112030,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE","time_elapsed":919709,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bfe"},"answer":"F and B starts their shifts,\nJ ends its shift at 12\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33013,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF","time_elapsed":534107,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c16"},"answer":"If you see the dot vertically above the 12 pm, then that is the shift that starts at 12 pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43585,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5","time_elapsed":835052,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c2e"},"answer":"Go to the X-axis and find 12pm, take the forward(right) diagonal up to each point on that line. Each of those points denote an event that starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":155577,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6","time_elapsed":807553,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c46"},"answer":"you look at the x axis and the you look at the points that correspond to the 12pm tick by creating an imaginary vertical line","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":40614,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX","time_elapsed":651145,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c76"},"answer":"Follow the diagonal line going from 12pm to the upper right","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26349,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J","time_elapsed":634498,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c8e"},"answer":"To determine this I go up vertically to find the points at 12 pm from the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"121","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":41552,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q","time_elapsed":1289655,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca6"},"answer":"look at the x-axis for 12pm, and view all the dots that align linearly","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43479,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P","time_elapsed":828566,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cbe"},"answer":"look at the x axes, which points is on the 12 pm label position ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33814,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK","time_elapsed":838941,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd6"},"answer":"well we look at the start/end time of the day at 12 then go up the y axis to see which letter is on the y axis of 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":69405,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W","time_elapsed":1074418,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cee"},"answer":"I look for the dot that lines up with 12pm to indicate that's when a shift starts. I also count back how many hours from dots passed 12pm to see if they also start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":52163,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ","time_elapsed":1182964,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d06"},"answer":"it is indicated on the horizontal axis\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37462,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU","time_elapsed":516685,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d1e"},"answer":"Find 12pm on the x-axis and then find the shift on the graph that has an x-coordinate of 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36506,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M","time_elapsed":729540,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d36"},"answer":"Looking at the x axis and the y axis. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":15863,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW","time_elapsed":636477,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d66"},"answer":"Look at dots above 12pm\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":24404,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY","time_elapsed":596049,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d7e"},"answer":"Follow the line that goes in a positive slope from the x axis where it says 12pm. So in this case it would be M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61932,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY","time_elapsed":700674,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d96"},"answer":"You follow the x axis to 12pm and then you go straight up the y axis from that 12pm point and if there is a dot along the y axis that corresponds to the 12pm on the x-axis, that shift starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":96009,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2","time_elapsed":725212,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dae"},"answer":"You check the x- axis and see which one correlates to the 12 pm time, whic his f and b","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34280,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK","time_elapsed":736838,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dde"},"answer":"you take 12pm on the X-axis and then go up along the vertical line to see which points lie on that line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":48725,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03","time_elapsed":821327,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df6"},"answer":"Which ever dots are aligned vertically with the 12pm marker on the horizontal axis\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":80406,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML","time_elapsed":922573,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e0e"},"answer":"by looking at the x axis you see above 12pm which events tart at that time ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":43653,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858","time_elapsed":480102,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e26"},"answer":"The point where the letter is on the graph is the start time, the end time is determined by the y-axis/duration. So, go to the 12pm tick mark on the axis and go up.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":63423,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY","time_elapsed":789950,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e3e"},"answer":"Look at the x-axis for 12pm. Any dots in that column begin at 12p","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26568,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP","time_elapsed":890267,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e56"},"answer":"Shifts B and F start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":26645,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER","time_elapsed":569154,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e6e"},"answer":"To determine which event starts at 12pm, look for 12pm on the x axis and then trace it vertically according to the diagram. This should tell you that at 12pm, shifts F and B fall on the same spots on the diagram, therefore showing that both shifts start at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":104984,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27","time_elapsed":1372742,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e86"},"answer":"Look in the x axis for 12pm then every entry above start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":35821,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP","time_elapsed":418197,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e9e"},"answer":"Looking at the x-axis, you find the label saying 12 pm. Then, you simply see which events align with the 12 pm marker. In this case, it would be events F and B.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114\n114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":113715,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU","time_elapsed":844416,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb6"},"answer":"The events at 12 pm can be determined by the x and y axis, along with the plotted points. The points that are directly above the 12 pm mark on the x axis are the events that start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":123519,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3","time_elapsed":996902,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ece"},"answer":"I look at the x-axis and find the 12PM time slot, then I look up to see which letters are directly above the 12 pm line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":69872,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43","time_elapsed":900074,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5efe"},"answer":"Each shift starts at 8am to 8pm and we look at the start and end time, specifically at 12. We noticed that B and F are lined up, making them the start","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72762,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7","time_elapsed":646877,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f16"},"answer":"If its point on the graph is after 12pm and the sum of the duration and at time at which it starts is before or on 8pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55166,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF","time_elapsed":744239,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f46"},"answer":"The vertical axis is the time duration and each point corresponds to 2 points on the horizontal axis, indicating the start and the end time (left-start; right-end). So for events starting at 12pm, I check the line going to North-east from 12pm and find M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":162115,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF","time_elapsed":975497,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f5e"},"answer":"F and B, make a vertical line at 12pm and look for the points in the line.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":46523,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM","time_elapsed":540871,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f76"},"answer":"Looking at the graph, the x-axis gives us the information as to when events start. To determine what even(s) start at 12pm we look at the 12-pm plot on the x-axis and look what points are in line with that point. In this case, shifts B and F start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":79949,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B","time_elapsed":721522,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f8e"},"answer":"Events that have a dot that is directly vertical to the 12pm mark.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":66388,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87","time_elapsed":804304,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa6"},"answer":"to see which letter(s) on the diagram points to 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":85662,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG","time_elapsed":610607,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fbe"},"answer":"all points that lay on the vertical x-intercept at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":67646,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC","time_elapsed":819413,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd6"},"answer":"I first look down at the bottom x-axis to find the start/end of the shifts. Locate 12pm and go up the triangle to find which shifts start at that time. In this scenario that would be B and F. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":57147,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7","time_elapsed":960910,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fee"},"answer":"Follow the diagonal line up so M and L","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":23550,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO","time_elapsed":618840,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6006"},"answer":"F and B start work at that hour of day because they are scheduled on that hour but they vary in how long they work. we could also tell that J ends work because they only work for two hours which means their shift ends at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":99583,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB","time_elapsed":1180452,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf601e"},"answer":"whatever event(s) is/are directly above 12 pm start(s) at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37754,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z","time_elapsed":843452,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6036"},"answer":"In one case, I could ignore the given lines and base it off of imaginary lines I made that follow the marks on the X-axis vertically. In another case, I could follow the lines of the graph which leads to that specific event. (In this case, M). I had trouble in the process interpreting the graph and have done both ways....","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":85637,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK","time_elapsed":1181855,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6066"},"answer":"Look for the points directly above 12PM on the x-axis","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":37434,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8","time_elapsed":669142,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf607e"},"answer":"spot the 12pm mark on the horizontal axis, trace the line that begins from 12pm mark in the triangle that is oriented towards the right, any letter dots that falls along this particular line start at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":154242,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z","time_elapsed":858929,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6096"},"answer":"determine where 12pm is on the chart, and travel up on a vertical line. every dot that is on that vertical line represents an event that starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":91811,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F","time_elapsed":809254,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ae"},"answer":"On the x axis of the graph, look where 12 pm is. Go straight up from 12 pm and the shifts that are there start at 12 pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":55731,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ","time_elapsed":524748,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c6"},"answer":"Look at the bottom axis of the graph that says START & END TIME. Find 12PM and look directly above it to see if any events land within that area. For this graph, events B and F start at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"113","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59415,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK","time_elapsed":944369,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60de"},"answer":"I go to the 12PM on the x-axis and then see if there are any dots on the y-axis centered at 12PM.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":48966,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4","time_elapsed":646769,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f6"},"answer":"Look at the 12 pm spot on the bottom axis and follow the diagonal line that's sloped to the right. Whichever nodes are on that line start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68197,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9","time_elapsed":674677,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf610e"},"answer":"Look at the x axis and see what points line up with 12 PM. (vertically)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47065,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU","time_elapsed":741024,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6126"},"answer":"Shifts that start at 12 pm are on the diaganol line that goes up and to the right of the 12pm mark. In this case M and L.\n\nBreaks that start at 12 pm are directly above the 12 pm mark.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61767,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K","time_elapsed":560723,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf613e"},"answer":"you look at the how many points are aligned with 12pm vertically","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59996,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X","time_elapsed":1001075,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6156"},"answer":"You find the time 12pm on the x axis of the graph and follow the line up to the left to see what ends and up to the right to see what is beginning","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"114","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":59844,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP","time_elapsed":849789,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf616e"},"answer":"I looked at the graph on the x-axis at the 12 pm mark and followed with my eye upwards all the points that fall along my imaginary eye line. \n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":58305,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN","time_elapsed":855926,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6186"},"answer":"To determine which event starts at 12pm. You look at the bottom of the chart with the labels of time. You find 12pm and anything that lays between the line upwards means that an event starts at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":75162,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72","time_elapsed":667006,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf619e"},"answer":"You look at 12PM at the bottom, and then follow the horizontal line going to the right.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":21301,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN","time_elapsed":545591,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b6"},"answer":"Follow the time axis until you hit 12pm, then follow the diagonal line going forward. On that diagonal line are the events that will start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":68276,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN","time_elapsed":537266,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ce"},"answer":"Look at the line that's diagonal to 12 PM. You have to look at the right line because that indicates when the events start.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34072,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L","time_elapsed":484609,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e6"},"answer":"FIND 12PM ON THE HORIZONTAL AXIS OF GRAPH AND FOLLOW DOTTED LINE UP-RIGHT. ALL OBJECTS THAT LIE ON THE DOTTED LINE START AT 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":56649,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1","time_elapsed":463818,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61fe"},"answer":"Shifts ending follow the diagonal left line, shifts starting follow the diagonal right line, coffee breaks are straight up from 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60165,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18","time_elapsed":544707,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6216"},"answer":"If the dot is on the 12pm line then the event starts at 12. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"115","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":169736,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ","time_elapsed":1270076,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6246"},"answer":"You can determine what events start at 12pm by following the lines on the side of the triangle that connects to the 12pm mark on the x-axis of the graph.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60110,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3","time_elapsed":564254,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6276"},"answer":"Look for points that start at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":25378,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H","time_elapsed":771143,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf628e"},"answer":"Look at the x axis where it says start & end time, then for starting, look at 12pm and go diagonally right which will hit the M and L.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":61719,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S","time_elapsed":650025,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a6"},"answer":"the dots on the diagonal line to the right ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34803,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58","time_elapsed":615356,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62be"},"answer":"Find 12pm on the x-axis and trace the line that is going upwards in the positive direction of the graph (so towards the right and up) from the 12pm tick mark. The dots found on this line are the shifts that start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":127546,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225","time_elapsed":874499,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d6"},"answer":"FOLLOW LINE\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":9220,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89","time_elapsed":771841,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ee"},"answer":"I find 12p on the bottom of the chart and follow the right slanted line. The shifts on this line begin at 12p.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":133999,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531","time_elapsed":845510,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6306"},"answer":"Let's say that the halfway mark of a shift is the top point of a triangle, then the starting point of a shift is the bottom left point, and the ending point is the bottom right point. Based on that structure, if a triangle had a bottom left point beginning at the 12PM mark, then the shift would start at the 12PM mark. (i.e. Shift M's left bottom point starts at 12PM, therefore Shift M starts at 12PM)","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":233339,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX","time_elapsed":1324058,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf631e"},"answer":"You first see which one on the x axis says start time at 12 pm.  ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84610,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG","time_elapsed":527356,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6336"},"answer":"Start at 12pm and follow the line to the right upward. Anything that aligns starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36020,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6","time_elapsed":561422,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf634e"},"answer":"Find 12 pm on the horizontal axis and follow the diagonal line that slopes upward. Any point along this line begins at 12","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":56960,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW","time_elapsed":1017401,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6366"},"answer":"Find 12 pm  on the x axis and trace up the right diagonal","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":29516,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993","time_elapsed":416846,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf637e"},"answer":"Follow the diagonal line from 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33357,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9","time_elapsed":1070382,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6396"},"answer":"DIAGONAL LINE GOING DOWN (TO THE LEFT) TO 12PM","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":36507,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS","time_elapsed":790879,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ae"},"answer":"By looking at the x-axis where 12pm is labeled then going upward to see what points are plotted","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":33049,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F","time_elapsed":766475,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c6"},"answer":"EVENT F AND B HAPPEN AT 12PM AND THIS CAN BE DETERMINED BY NOTING WHAT POINTS FOLLOW WITHIN A HYPOTHETICAL VERTICAL LINE DRAWN THROUGH THE Y AXIS FROM THE 12PM POINT ON THE X AXIS","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":82385,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM","time_elapsed":1000024,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63de"},"answer":"First you find 12pm along the axis representing times of day, the x axis. There are two lines that intersect at that point. The right one represents start time while the left shows end time. So to find what starts at 12pm, follow the right line. All events on that line start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":106656,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ","time_elapsed":765547,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f6"},"answer":"Find 2 pm on the x-axis. Then from there follow the diagonal line that goes upright from that point. Any point that falls on that line starts at 12pm","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":65281,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4","time_elapsed":785843,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf640e"},"answer":"On the x-axis, find 12. Then find the horizontal line going upwards to the left (like a positive slope) connected to 12 on the x-axis. All points on this line start at 12.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":95341,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C","time_elapsed":699308,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6426"},"answer":"TO SEE WHO STARTS THEIR SHIFT AT 12 PM, YOU LOOK AT THE 12 PM MARK ON THE X AXIS AND LOOK AT WHICH LETTERS LIE ON ITS RIGHT DIAGONAL LINE. TO SEE WHO ENDS THEIR SHIFT AT 12 PM, YOU LOOK AT WHICH LETTERS LIE ON ITS LEFT DIAGONAL LINE.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311\n311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":130060,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5","time_elapsed":865585,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf643e"},"answer":"You go to 12 pm on the x-axis then follow the line going upwards and to the right. The points on that line start at 12 pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":44365,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3","time_elapsed":218745,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf646e"},"answer":"The diagonal line that goes through M and L indicate that those two shifts start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":72985,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5","time_elapsed":1005428,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6486"},"answer":"You look at the bottom axis and look for 12pm. Once you've determined that point you follow it up along the right hand side line and which ever point you encounter along that line is what events start at 12pm. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":51019,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217","time_elapsed":866875,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf649e"},"answer":"Find 12pm on the x-axis. The point has two diagonals that stem from it. Look at the diagonal stemming from 12pm that points to the right. As you move up the diagonal, any points on that line has a start time of 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"311","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":83964,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2","time_elapsed":728749,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b6"},"answer":"By looking at the diagnol, M and L starts and by looking vertically F and B starts coffee breaks","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":53617,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG","time_elapsed":722907,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ce"},"answer":"You can determine which shifts occur at 12 by seeing which points on the line coming out of 12 towards the right. Breaks that occur at 12pm are points on the horizontal line above 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":82645,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH","time_elapsed":947765,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e6"},"answer":"In this triangular graph, the left bottom side is the start of a shift, whose pinnacle is the label of the shift. So we look for 12pm on the x axis and follow the positive gradient until a label is reached","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":102789,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM","time_elapsed":929977,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64fe"},"answer":"You look at the x-axis and find the point that says 12 pm and then see which events lie above the 12 pm mark.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":31163,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM","time_elapsed":871594,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6516"},"answer":"Go up the diagonal line to the right until you find a letter.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":39649,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H","time_elapsed":472707,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf652e"},"answer":"Shift B and F","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":34414,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN","time_elapsed":707559,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6546"},"answer":"Shifts B and F are in their coffee break, and shifts M and L are just starting. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":60775,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H","time_elapsed":1026818,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf655e"},"answer":"Trace the diagonal line the starts at 12 pm and scales up the right of the screen. Whatever points fall on that line are the shifts that start at 12pm.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":86578,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS","time_elapsed":697994,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6576"},"answer":"Follow the x axis, then look at the diagonal to determine the duration.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":47558,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B","time_elapsed":1262552,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf658e"},"answer":"look for dots aligned with the dash on the x-axis corresponding to the 12 PM ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":84684,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP","time_elapsed":1142035,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a6"},"answer":"LOOK AT THE START AND END TIME AXIS\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":16782,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M","time_elapsed":1192723,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65be"},"answer":"To find out which shifts start at 12 pm you look at the x axis at the point that corresponds to 12pm then follow the diagonal line up and to the right. In this case it would be M and L. Conversely, to see which shifts end at 12 you would go diagonally up and to the left. In this case there are none. To see which shift have a break at 12 you just go vertically up from 12 pm. In this case B and F.","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":266563,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J","time_elapsed":1207898,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d6"},"answer":"The line left of the point is when it starts\n","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":32092,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4","time_elapsed":1185018,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ee"},"answer":"follow the diagonal line that corresponds with the start time. For 12 pm the starting shifts (displayed to the right of the line) are M and  L. ","block":"triangular_testing","condition":"211","experiment":"2YP3","graph":"triangular","internal_node_id":"0.0-7.0-0.0","q":16,"rt":115440,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG","time_elapsed":1154652,"trial_index":20,"trial_type":"html","url":"../views/src/external/stimulus.html"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b15"},"answer":"A","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14701,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b16"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12358,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b17"},"answer":"Z","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11473,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b18"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26421,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b19"},"answer":"F","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":53386,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9535,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13439,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1c"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":16087,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1d"},"answer":"I","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19177,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1e"},"answer":"X","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":31042,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b1f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10003,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b20"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10702,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b21"},"answer":"FX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12918,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b22"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12039,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b23"},"answer":"EF","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":53994,"session":"bravo","subject":"KGNTA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b2c"},"answer":"HJKUDEBCAIO","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36194,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b2d"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11697,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b2e"},"answer":"JD","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16893,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b2f"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9324,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b30"},"answer":"JD","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":17753,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b31"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":29456,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b32"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17508,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b33"},"answer":"M","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24446,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b34"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14840,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b35"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5534,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b36"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12391,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b37"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14605,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b38"},"answer":"LH","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20309,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b39"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17984,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b3a"},"answer":"JF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18192,"session":"bravo","subject":"YFBWR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b43"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21302,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b44"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15282,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b45"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41473,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b46"},"answer":"HJ","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14976,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b47"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11570,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b48"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17358,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b49"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24817,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4a"},"answer":"IE","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36859,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4b"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18407,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4c"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18405,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10307,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4e"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5661,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b4f"},"answer":"AG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23770,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b50"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12194,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b51"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17730,"session":"bravo","subject":"6DN76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5a"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16885,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5b"},"answer":"D","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13711,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26302,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5d"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53404,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5e"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":35414,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b5f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7409,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b60"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":11714,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b61"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31504,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b62"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17182,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b63"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19870,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b64"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7422,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b65"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7162,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b66"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25352,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b67"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39716,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b68"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":32469,"session":"bravo","subject":"73N5W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b71"},"answer":"F","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":72808,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b72"},"answer":"K","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23045,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b73"},"answer":"F","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34012,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b74"},"answer":"H","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9668,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b75"},"answer":"O","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22346,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b76"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7686,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b77"},"answer":"XO","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25915,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b78"},"answer":"G","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":20700,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b79"},"answer":"I","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":52555,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7a"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8748,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7b"},"answer":"ML","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11690,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7c"},"answer":"G","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5570,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7d"},"answer":"HN","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14424,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7e"},"answer":"X","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11462,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b7f"},"answer":"KX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27620,"session":"bravo","subject":"7E6TJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b88"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23499,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b89"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10443,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8a"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7001,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8b"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44095,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8c"},"answer":"HU","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":55530,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17322,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18410,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b8f"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":20666,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b90"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28449,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b91"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14554,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b92"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10026,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b93"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8471,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b94"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13337,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b95"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9702,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b96"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21928,"session":"bravo","subject":"YS42C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4b9f"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38858,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba0"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":67941,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18827,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba2"},"answer":"FU","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27625,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba3"},"answer":"OF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":70173,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5392,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12207,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba6"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23652,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba7"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10903,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba8"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5793,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ba9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12479,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4baa"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5153,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15146,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bac"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":37465,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18359,"session":"bravo","subject":"GKC1Y"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bb6"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":77932,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bb7"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30524,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bb8"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13187,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bb9"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5433,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bba"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":19447,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bbb"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5753,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bbc"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19842,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bbd"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51160,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bbe"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":49327,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bbf"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7682,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bc0"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10521,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bc1"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8240,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bc2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24847,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bc3"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8993,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bc4"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12183,"session":"bravo","subject":"FBLXY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bcd"},"answer":"F","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25418,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bce"},"answer":"K","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25100,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bcf"},"answer":"F","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18559,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd0"},"answer":"H","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11548,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd1"},"answer":"O","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":42802,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd2"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13366,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26004,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd4"},"answer":"G","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35937,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd5"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":43083,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd6"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7479,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd7"},"answer":"ML","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18830,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd8"},"answer":"G","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8020,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bd9"},"answer":"EF","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15337,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bda"},"answer":"X","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10219,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bdb"},"answer":"KX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23587,"session":"bravo","subject":"2492T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be4"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13635,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be5"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16361,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be6"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":64816,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be7"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16542,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be8"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12920,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4be9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10121,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bea"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":50244,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4beb"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":70234,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bec"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13693,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bed"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6770,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bee"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12892,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bef"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8185,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bf0"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10122,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bf1"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8850,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bf2"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17887,"session":"bravo","subject":"8XBVF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bfb"},"answer":"A","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26156,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bfc"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":47034,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bfd"},"answer":"Z","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22591,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bfe"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55231,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4bff"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":49933,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c00"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7740,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c01"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29651,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c02"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":27693,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c03"},"answer":"I","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22939,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c04"},"answer":"X","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19033,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c05"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14914,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c06"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":23019,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c07"},"answer":"FX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32014,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c08"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":29927,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c09"},"answer":"EF","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38315,"session":"bravo","subject":"TMVBA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c12"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25115,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c13"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30409,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c14"},"answer":"AUB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32590,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c15"},"answer":"DE","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9060,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c16"},"answer":"HK","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":63731,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c17"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25061,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c18"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":66370,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c19"},"answer":"AK","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49389,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1a"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13034,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1b"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6482,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11825,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1d"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7822,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1e"},"answer":"HN","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22924,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c1f"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20390,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c20"},"answer":"FN","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18187,"session":"bravo","subject":"WWOFR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c40"},"answer":"A","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26588,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c41"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18361,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c42"},"answer":"Z","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14006,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c43"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30818,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c44"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":83069,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c45"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6997,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c46"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23620,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c47"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45127,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c48"},"answer":"I","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20672,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c49"},"answer":"X","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48014,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c4a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11725,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c4b"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14057,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c4c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24469,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c4d"},"answer":"","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":43313,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c4e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":40348,"session":"bravo","subject":"WJWFF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c57"},"answer":"CF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38926,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c58"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20437,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c59"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22203,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5a"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":35123,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5b"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":140081,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11128,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":50481,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5e"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45634,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c5f"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41626,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c60"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7234,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c61"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10004,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c62"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7994,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c63"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16719,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c64"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15002,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c65"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80160,"session":"bravo","subject":"TELDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c6e"},"answer":"C","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":61750,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c6f"},"answer":"D","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":57543,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c70"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26964,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c71"},"answer":"DE","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19723,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c72"},"answer":"","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":46501,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c73"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17170,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c74"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30470,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c75"},"answer":"IJEGCHZND","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":97963,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c76"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20605,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c77"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22895,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c78"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13263,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c79"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14002,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c7a"},"answer":"EX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":69547,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c7b"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17375,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c7c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36372,"session":"bravo","subject":"WLDKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c85"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15151,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c86"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28506,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c87"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15633,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c88"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46405,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c89"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":112735,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8143,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28678,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8c"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42263,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8d"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30655,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8e"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":32923,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c8f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22904,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c90"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8240,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c91"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24901,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c92"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16504,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c93"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":64570,"session":"bravo","subject":"G92Y8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c9c"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74149,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c9d"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":52269,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c9e"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52717,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4c9f"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":91088,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca0"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":27016,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10425,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21444,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca3"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35596,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca4"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17489,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca5"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41235,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8639,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca7"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12968,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca8"},"answer":"EX","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":44439,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ca9"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23838,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4caa"},"answer":"EB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39847,"session":"bravo","subject":"94NZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb3"},"answer":"A","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":58207,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb4"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31047,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb5"},"answer":"Z","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26592,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb6"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":60359,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb7"},"answer":"U","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":165609,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb8"},"answer":"EG","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6681,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cb9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28877,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cba"},"answer":"E","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33708,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cbb"},"answer":"I","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14094,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cbc"},"answer":"J","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16336,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cbd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13396,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cbe"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9431,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cbf"},"answer":"FX","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":52107,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cc0"},"answer":"B","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23868,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cc1"},"answer":"ON","axis":"partial","condition":"112","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41576,"session":"bravo","subject":"HYNA2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce1"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17880,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce2"},"answer":"D","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42236,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce3"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":37727,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce4"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":25520,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce5"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":117547,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce6"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10373,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce7"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22199,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce8"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32053,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ce9"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17611,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cea"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":94656,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ceb"},"answer":"MAGCKXOPLHZND","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":63117,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cec"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12329,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ced"},"answer":"XZ","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18987,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cee"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":43279,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cef"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":94756,"session":"bravo","subject":"10XMB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cf8"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":71900,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cf9"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":152081,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cfa"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22185,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cfb"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":104123,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cfc"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":105123,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cfd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17315,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cfe"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16018,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4cff"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28495,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d00"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":299600,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d01"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9348,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d02"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12278,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d03"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19525,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d04"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":63067,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d05"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":32792,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d06"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":61593,"session":"mouse","subject":"ZNVCQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d0f"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":90173,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d10"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":68297,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d11"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33259,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d12"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":80223,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d13"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":164115,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d14"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17692,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d15"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32186,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d16"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":63838,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d17"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26250,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d18"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":32028,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d19"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12956,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d1a"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10911,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d1b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":44972,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d1c"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34660,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d1d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37532,"session":"mouse","subject":"7PEXQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d26"},"answer":"CF","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":102460,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d27"},"answer":"KD","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":57883,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d28"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":146715,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d29"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":41624,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2a"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":86340,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":40939,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27793,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2d"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":77173,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2e"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53925,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d2f"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":79389,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d30"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15723,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d31"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10292,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d32"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19090,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d33"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":55495,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d34"},"answer":"BX","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":75151,"session":"mouse","subject":"BF80A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d54"},"answer":"AO","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":116809,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d55"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":51253,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d56"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":138986,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d57"},"answer":"D","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":103127,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d58"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":161155,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d59"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12031,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":90894,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5b"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42869,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5c"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30038,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5d"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":63627,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":24694,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d5f"},"answer":"PLH","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":47747,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d60"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":89028,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d61"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40030,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d62"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":54760,"session":"mouse","subject":"PRXGX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d6b"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":162148,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d6c"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18754,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d6d"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25621,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d6e"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11813,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d6f"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":117778,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d70"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9806,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d71"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39057,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d72"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":157784,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d73"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":61588,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d74"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":27355,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d75"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22985,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d76"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16961,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d77"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16090,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d78"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27923,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d79"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14656,"session":"mouse","subject":"VKOJQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d82"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":129231,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d83"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":47892,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d84"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":80056,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d85"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":29668,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d86"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29580,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d87"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15572,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d88"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":58320,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d89"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46923,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8a"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":66836,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8b"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19616,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8c"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15553,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8d"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":22029,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30219,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d8f"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12272,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d90"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21094,"session":"mouse","subject":"TWVNQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d99"},"answer":"AF","axis":"full","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":60225,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9a"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21644,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9b"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14910,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9c"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16602,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9d"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77015,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":48612,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4d9f"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23992,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da0"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44820,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da1"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34081,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da2"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5731,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da3"},"answer":"BML","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12134,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da4"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9077,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17335,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da6"},"answer":"BX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22090,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4da7"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27436,"session":"won","subject":"1ZY3L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db0"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":55122,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db1"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42767,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db2"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":137439,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db3"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":103801,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db4"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":242844,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db5"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":28358,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":94293,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db7"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60928,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db8"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48728,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4db9"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18259,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dba"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11982,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dbb"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10839,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dbc"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":85890,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dbd"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13761,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dbe"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80581,"session":"mouse","subject":"B2GMH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dc7"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":199885,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dc8"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":48336,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dc9"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22461,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dca"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53493,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dcb"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":127395,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dcc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20811,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dcd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":51695,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dce"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":74782,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dcf"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":95956,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd0"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10884,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14907,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd2"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18578,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16296,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd4"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9113,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dd5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41005,"session":"mouse","subject":"RGPN4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dde"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":34394,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ddf"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13766,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13167,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de1"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":74963,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de2"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":216639,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11794,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14287,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de5"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":58911,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de6"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21009,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de7"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":59400,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8158,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4de9"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10497,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dea"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24280,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4deb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18303,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dec"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19610,"session":"won","subject":"DQQQX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4df5"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23437,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4df6"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12822,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4df7"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19434,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4df8"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21592,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4df9"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91776,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dfa"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8626,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dfb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25454,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dfc"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49080,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dfd"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":57868,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dfe"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48595,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4dff"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11504,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e00"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9291,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e01"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25055,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e02"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":56164,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e03"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47359,"session":"won","subject":"VJNWA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e0c"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50301,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e0d"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40191,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e0e"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25167,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e0f"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39005,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e10"},"answer":"OX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58688,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e11"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11330,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e12"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16842,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e13"},"answer":"JM","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":82955,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e14"},"answer":"M","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15587,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e15"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15406,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e16"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":41674,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e17"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8939,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e18"},"answer":"HZ","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57637,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e19"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23526,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e1a"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18061,"session":"t00","subject":"FU11G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3a"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":57191,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3b"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46375,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3c"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24353,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3d"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24346,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3e"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29416,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e3f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10231,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e40"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":53428,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e41"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51390,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e42"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":119385,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e43"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11543,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e44"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9947,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e45"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":23204,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e46"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15134,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e47"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17910,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e48"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":4.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18654,"session":"too","subject":"4FETN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e51"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":63168,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e52"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":83486,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e53"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19915,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e54"},"answer":"J","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":37333,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e55"},"answer":"HK","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":50645,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e56"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21901,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e57"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19494,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e58"},"answer":"IJND","axis":"full","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":64436,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e59"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":64776,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5a"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41356,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13512,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5c"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11553,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5d"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":43145,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5e"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27544,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e5f"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46335,"session":"t00","subject":"CKRHQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e68"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50148,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e69"},"answer":"D","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":111385,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6a"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33557,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6b"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53985,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6c"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75085,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8185,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13905,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e6f"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37540,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e70"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37000,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e71"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25663,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e72"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7655,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e73"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11870,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e74"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":37148,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e75"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":59071,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e76"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":99846,"session":"too","subject":"9393C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e7f"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29268,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e80"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8594,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e81"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":7765,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e82"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45292,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e83"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":52639,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e84"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6399,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e85"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15457,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e86"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":27496,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e87"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14418,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e88"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":29988,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e89"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7843,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e8a"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7801,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e8b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24716,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e8c"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":62611,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e8d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36979,"session":"tree","subject":"S4G9E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e96"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":112983,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e97"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11541,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e98"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11261,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e99"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7994,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9a"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13877,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6664,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9c"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":47760,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9d"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73856,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9e"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18773,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4e9f"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14822,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ea0"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12022,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ea1"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15208,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ea2"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15515,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ea3"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9971,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ea4"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23736,"session":"tree","subject":"L0W0F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ead"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50681,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eae"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25043,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eaf"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":80184,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb0"},"answer":"D","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":103655,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb1"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":116824,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb2"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11500,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21135,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb4"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49906,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb5"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36481,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb6"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":86663,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb7"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10175,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb8"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13728,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eb9"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27405,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eba"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":55205,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ebb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":68709,"session":"flower","subject":"ZJPX1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec4"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7223,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec5"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6292,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec6"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31775,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec7"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32650,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec8"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18066,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ec9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5022,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eca"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12988,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ecb"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":15441,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ecc"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":8854,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ecd"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20457,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ece"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9326,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ecf"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5332,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ed0"},"answer":"CX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20413,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ed1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21903,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ed2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28280,"session":"sox","subject":"JZWPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef2"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36889,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef3"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12567,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef4"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32376,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef5"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44547,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef6"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":98364,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8496,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef8"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27286,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ef9"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34454,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4efa"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":64227,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4efb"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":51886,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4efc"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":20470,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4efd"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11695,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4efe"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31816,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4eff"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47358,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f00"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":54724,"session":"fire","subject":"DD3DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f09"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19376,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0a"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17248,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0b"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39615,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0c"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":49800,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0d"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":85706,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16774,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f0f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20849,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f10"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45567,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f11"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19792,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f12"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":57254,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f13"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17644,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f14"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19642,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f15"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":58268,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f16"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":53542,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f17"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":89151,"session":"fire","subject":"OVZHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f20"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33571,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f21"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29610,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f22"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":40300,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f23"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8567,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f24"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11414,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f25"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9404,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f26"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33335,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f27"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":66887,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f28"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18537,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f29"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8162,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f2a"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7057,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f2b"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10571,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f2c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10167,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f2d"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":4661,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f2e"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12770,"session":"sox","subject":"J2MPW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f37"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36237,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f38"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15563,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f39"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39877,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3a"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44333,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3b"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":153699,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8642,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14888,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3e"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43117,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f3f"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22077,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f40"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44209,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f41"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10583,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f42"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11621,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f43"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":59418,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f44"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":51948,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f45"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":108508,"session":"fire","subject":"XX1TE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f4e"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41071,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f4f"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16548,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f50"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16394,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f51"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":31930,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f52"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":57625,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f53"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9230,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f54"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18713,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f55"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35176,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f56"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40405,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f57"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":79096,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f58"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11501,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f59"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11704,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f5a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":40749,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f5b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30159,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f5c"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37276,"session":"fire","subject":"B4LD9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f65"},"answer":"CF","axis":"full","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":71169,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f66"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15887,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f67"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21468,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f68"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19294,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f69"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20997,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6a"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11607,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6b"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26974,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6c"},"answer":"J","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52655,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6d"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17013,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6e"},"answer":"P","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":40191,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f6f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8216,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f70"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7918,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f71"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":58598,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f72"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":29590,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f73"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":84018,"session":"sox","subject":"QY1F7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f7c"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70878,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f7d"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":69494,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f7e"},"answer":"AH","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41248,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f7f"},"answer":"D","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":31136,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f80"},"answer":"J","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":87040,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f81"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10065,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f82"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28560,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f83"},"answer":"IEFG","axis":"full","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":62532,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f84"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30436,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f85"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11914,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f86"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18054,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f87"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8561,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f88"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41153,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f89"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":65021,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f8a"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":68915,"session":"sox","subject":"TVQKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f93"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":52822,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f94"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":38072,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f95"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27780,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f96"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53117,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f97"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":90134,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f98"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10605,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f99"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31523,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9a"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50124,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9b"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37455,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9c"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":71759,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21776,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9e"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13202,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4f9f"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":73414,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fa0"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":48162,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fa1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":49454,"session":"fire","subject":"8LGZ4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4faa"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31511,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fab"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26704,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fac"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41536,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fad"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24900,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fae"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":33007,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4faf"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8567,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb0"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":43512,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb1"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":62392,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb2"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27331,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb3"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25660,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb4"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":26142,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb5"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":23370,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb6"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30226,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb7"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13080,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fb8"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18928,"session":"heaven","subject":"HJ5O5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc1"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31200,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc2"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9722,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc3"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13187,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc4"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":25865,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc5"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30946,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc6"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5727,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc7"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18344,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc8"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30134,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fc9"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19401,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fca"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":36317,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fcb"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8126,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fcc"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9363,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fcd"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22462,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fce"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22930,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fcf"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":4.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":72698,"session":"taine","subject":"YKJOR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fd8"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24618,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fd9"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12573,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fda"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10741,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fdb"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12416,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fdc"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13762,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fdd"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17477,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fde"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24963,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fdf"},"answer":"IJEOHZND","axis":"full","clicks":8,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47021,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe0"},"answer":"IF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":61973,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe1"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18726,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8606,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe3"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6045,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe4"},"answer":"LH","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21865,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe5"},"answer":"O","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9067,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fe6"},"answer":"C","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37331,"session":"taine","subject":"PQN6T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4fef"},"answer":"CF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":79982,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff0"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22585,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff1"},"answer":"AOU","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49147,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff2"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":118961,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff3"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":36881,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25508,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff5"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":76075,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff6"},"answer":"C","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54343,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff7"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24453,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6442,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ff9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14936,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ffa"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":52890,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ffb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27719,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ffc"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17546,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf4ffd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44144,"session":"sox","subject":"6MWHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5006"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46519,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5007"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12826,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5008"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19451,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5009"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":85146,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500a"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":83280,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9574,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19498,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500d"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51582,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500e"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19629,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf500f"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":71994,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5010"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9097,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5011"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18318,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5012"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41944,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5013"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39195,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5014"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47838,"session":"heaven","subject":"QUCDX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5034"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23530,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5035"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9569,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5036"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15324,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5037"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":64940,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5038"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":76826,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5039"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8871,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19503,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503b"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":63715,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503c"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29830,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503d"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22575,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503e"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8392,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf503f"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7345,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5040"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":44643,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5041"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21673,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5042"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47879,"session":"men","subject":"VXAHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf504b"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11336,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf504c"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19019,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf504d"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33402,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf504e"},"answer":"DE","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13239,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf504f"},"answer":"HE","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":56279,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5050"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6365,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5051"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37651,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5052"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23298,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5053"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16394,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5054"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17869,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5055"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7304,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5056"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6526,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5057"},"answer":"FG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50104,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5058"},"answer":"","axis":"diagonal","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11695,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5059"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36393,"session":"men","subject":"N8G60"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5062"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22853,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5063"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14673,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5064"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14063,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5065"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":6.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":87230,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5066"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":102175,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5067"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10331,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5068"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24121,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5069"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50420,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506a"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42667,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506b"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":76558,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11447,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506d"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8398,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506e"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23406,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf506f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":73893,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5070"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28726,"session":"thine","subject":"J994U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5079"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":53503,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507a"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23917,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507b"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":107222,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507c"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":123736,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507d"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":67152,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507e"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21128,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf507f"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18794,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5080"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":87336,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5081"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19428,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5082"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":43640,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5083"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12375,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5084"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12115,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5085"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29237,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5086"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33707,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5087"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":69587,"session":"heaven","subject":"BKTUJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50a7"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74092,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50a8"},"answer":"K","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40375,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50a9"},"answer":"F","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10146,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50aa"},"answer":"H","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18002,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ab"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":57981,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":37543,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ad"},"answer":"XO","axis":"full","clicks":6,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":87925,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ae"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73174,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50af"},"answer":"IE","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":65838,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b0"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11581,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13408,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b2"},"answer":"G","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11484,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10750,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b4"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6020,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50b5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"full","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63896,"session":"sox","subject":"X9GRY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50be"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32450,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50bf"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10597,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c0"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":173730,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c1"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":48464,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c2"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21630,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c3"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6074,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c4"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21114,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c5"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43179,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c6"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41580,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c7"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8975,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c8"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19070,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50c9"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":24055,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ca"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11550,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50cb"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7405,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50cc"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19913,"session":"men","subject":"08WET"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50d5"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15980,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50d6"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14347,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20703,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50d8"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":73800,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50d9"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":43930,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50da"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9777,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50db"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30695,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50dc"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59202,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50dd"},"answer":"IM","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":64610,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50de"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11739,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50df"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9816,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50e0"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14430,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50e1"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46983,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50e2"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31829,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50e3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44180,"session":"men","subject":"HWJDK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ec"},"answer":"A","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41493,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ed"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17118,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ee"},"answer":"Z","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13974,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50ef"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45072,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f0"},"answer":"U","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75444,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f1"},"answer":"EG","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7954,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f2"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14113,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f3"},"answer":"E","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52556,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f4"},"answer":"I","axis":"full","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27370,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f5"},"answer":"X","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":31837,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f6"},"answer":"FB","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13087,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f7"},"answer":"B","axis":"full","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10433,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":99109,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50f9"},"answer":"","axis":"full","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40414,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf50fa"},"answer":"EF","axis":"full","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":36166,"session":"thine","subject":"KYTVX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5103"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24653,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5104"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17565,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5105"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14104,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5106"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21366,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5107"},"answer":"XU","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":31912,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5108"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":24394,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5109"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":50653,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510a"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55288,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510b"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22675,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510c"},"answer":"J","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19400,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12737,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510e"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13414,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf510f"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":118386,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5110"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36626,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5111"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":43152,"session":"men","subject":"8U980"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511a"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19735,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511b"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17618,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511c"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18934,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511d"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":71858,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511e"},"answer":"IU","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":97655,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf511f"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8923,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5120"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30516,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5121"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55492,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5122"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47530,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5123"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52335,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5124"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14662,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5125"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":22679,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5126"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30915,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5127"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23854,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5128"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39046,"session":"men","subject":"FY6UN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5131"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29751,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5132"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10998,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5133"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16489,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5134"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":66731,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5135"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":116399,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5136"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10836,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5137"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31303,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5138"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53991,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5139"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":59357,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513a"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":66156,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12971,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513c"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":37977,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513d"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26956,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513e"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":32204,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf513f"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":72373,"session":"men","subject":"LPABX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5148"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":83764,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5149"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24882,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514a"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20009,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514b"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10214,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514c"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":52905,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514d"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12583,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514e"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":96332,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf514f"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":80205,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5150"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":106097,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5151"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15758,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5152"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11172,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5153"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12212,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5154"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20791,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5155"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14806,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5156"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33574,"session":"men","subject":"T2OHS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf515f"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15634,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5160"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17511,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5161"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16284,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5162"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":118575,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5163"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91250,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5164"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10138,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5165"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37364,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5166"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59182,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5167"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18261,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5168"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44497,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5169"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9034,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf516a"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11207,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf516b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23209,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf516c"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33936,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf516d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27052,"session":"men","subject":"4KEEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5176"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33002,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5177"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22649,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5178"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52829,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5179"},"answer":"DE","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56886,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517a"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30692,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517b"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9388,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517c"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30764,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517d"},"answer":"OHZND","axis":"diagonal","clicks":5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":98036,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517e"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":51425,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf517f"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":33142,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5180"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":29339,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5181"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18354,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5182"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":97553,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5183"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":44336,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5184"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":62042,"session":"men","subject":"E3YN6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf518d"},"answer":"C","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36633,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf518e"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20638,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf518f"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23924,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5190"},"answer":"DE","axis":"diagonal","clicks":24.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":93732,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5191"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":45039,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5192"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12504,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5193"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25607,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5194"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":110841,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5195"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24032,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5196"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":133900,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5197"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14675,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5198"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10074,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5199"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36138,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf519a"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":76404,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf519b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":64540,"session":"men","subject":"TCH5L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a4"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31329,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a5"},"answer":"J","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12576,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a6"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39226,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a7"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16194,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a8"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12773,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51a9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8561,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51aa"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34848,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ab"},"answer":"AKO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":5.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":16963,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ac"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33425,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ad"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22425,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ae"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19234,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51af"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9185,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51b0"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21766,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51b1"},"answer":"","axis":"diagonal","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11156,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51b2"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23372,"session":"men","subject":"FA0KM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51bb"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35360,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51bc"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30852,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51bd"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":30314,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51be"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":79307,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51bf"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":90667,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c0"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8743,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24549,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c2"},"answer":"IJM","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67849,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c3"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":68395,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c4"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":46706,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17514,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c6"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17557,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c7"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16032,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c8"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42123,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51c9"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":73091,"session":"men","subject":"OY8PV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d2"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21458,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d3"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27872,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d4"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25028,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d5"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32820,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d6"},"answer":"J","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44814,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d7"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":33380,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d8"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":56794,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51d9"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53096,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51da"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28242,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51db"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":64130,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51dc"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":23394,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51dd"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18188,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51de"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28770,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51df"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10022,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51e0"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":83298,"session":"men","subject":"93YLJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51e9"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":173420,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ea"},"answer":"K","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15938,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51eb"},"answer":"F","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13586,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ec"},"answer":"H","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6840,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ed"},"answer":"O","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22294,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ee"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10876,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51ef"},"answer":"XO","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44434,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f0"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":75884,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f1"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33134,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f2"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19948,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f3"},"answer":"ML","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15774,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f4"},"answer":"G","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20258,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20348,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f6"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9406,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf51f7"},"answer":"KX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19174,"session":"men","subject":"7VQV2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5200"},"answer":"A","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10727,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5201"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16158,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5202"},"answer":"Z","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27055,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5203"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":62053,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5204"},"answer":"U","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":210249,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5205"},"answer":"EG","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11584,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5206"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35851,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5207"},"answer":"E","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":86727,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5208"},"answer":"I","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36626,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5209"},"answer":"X","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":110815,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf520a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16501,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf520b"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12167,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf520c"},"answer":"FX","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49560,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf520d"},"answer":"B","axis":"diagonal","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":161471,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf520e"},"answer":"EF","axis":"diagonal","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80834,"session":"men","subject":"JDT07"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5217"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19706,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5218"},"answer":"K","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11298,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5219"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9407,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9211,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15827,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16969,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17677,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49915,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf521f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44757,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5220"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9445,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5221"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6958,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5222"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17662,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5223"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21477,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5224"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10769,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5225"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18542,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZUJQV"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf522f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16907,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5230"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12470,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5231"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12870,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5232"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55995,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5233"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58244,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5234"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7977,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5235"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30572,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5236"},"answer":"EGC","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56000,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5237"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40289,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5238"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8598,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5239"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10569,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf523a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5323,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf523b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39420,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf523c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23282,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf523d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":43772,"session":"kilo","subject":"XKNWZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5247"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18294,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5248"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9439,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5249"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22276,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":50729,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":110835,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9372,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21775,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44323,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf524f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33575,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5250"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":35747,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5251"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14771,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5252"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9049,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5253"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30462,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5254"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":50560,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5255"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":91813,"session":"kilo","subject":"ZB1L5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf525f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":42994,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5260"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16299,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5261"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16058,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5262"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24901,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5263"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":104537,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5264"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7711,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5265"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28594,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5266"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37547,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5267"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21012,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5268"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":34051,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5269"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9713,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf526a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5661,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf526b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19396,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf526c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":25964,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf526d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":53035,"session":"kilo","subject":"3Z8ZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5277"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31846,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5278"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15163,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5279"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15009,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":72242,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":202174,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11697,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25750,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51036,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf527f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17805,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5280"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":60721,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5281"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12158,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5282"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8602,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5283"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20258,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5284"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":57312,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5285"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":59268,"session":"kilo","subject":"FN9LT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf528f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36321,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5290"},"answer":"K","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13110,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5291"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":35453,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5292"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":84593,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5293"},"answer":"H","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":35244,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5294"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16068,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5295"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":46294,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5296"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94882,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5297"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":79947,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5298"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44330,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5299"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15972,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf529a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14777,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf529b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57196,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf529c"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":49446,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf529d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18413,"session":"kilo","subject":"M3NXB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52a7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32011,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52a8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16190,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52a9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27855,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52aa"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":61015,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ab"},"answer":"OJD","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":38709,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6462,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ad"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25917,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ae"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37643,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52af"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26065,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":34613,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":22969,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10119,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":64606,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b4"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40388,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52b5"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45544,"session":"kilo","subject":"SWST4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52bf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21399,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":57761,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21628,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56034,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":149096,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10460,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25542,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31756,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18476,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44784,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52c9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10303,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ca"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19803,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52cb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20974,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52cc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34980,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52cd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":53123,"session":"kilo","subject":"WBR05"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19535,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52d8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16944,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52d9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16636,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52da"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":60930,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52db"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":116211,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7347,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52dd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20483,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52de"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35719,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":76145,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":54567,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8690,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7969,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":61342,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":50825,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52e5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":72319,"session":"kilo","subject":"X66XB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52ef"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28464,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9690,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14486,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44380,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":98557,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10373,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35574,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25542,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41517,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f8"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9634,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52f9"},"answer":"M","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7161,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52fa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3985,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52fb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25151,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52fc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17545,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf52fd"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25358,"session":"kilo","subject":"K2YPP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5307"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50771,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5308"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13809,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5309"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18917,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":20357,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25802,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22138,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":40857,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55077,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf530f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42751,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5310"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10814,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5311"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13615,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5312"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17212,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5313"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24170,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5314"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7312,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5315"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11276,"session":"lima","subject":"RV9F6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf531f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74973,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5320"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":33255,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5321"},"answer":"UE","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":68522,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5322"},"answer":"H","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":74878,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5323"},"answer":"O","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":88609,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5324"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20429,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5325"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":68768,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5326"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":81890,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5327"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":113784,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5328"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":51609,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5329"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":29898,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf532a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16269,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf532b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28156,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf532c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8928,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf532d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":210688,"session":"kilo","subject":"NVGH4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5337"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27718,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5338"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":51745,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5339"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19562,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":94532,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":197695,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15589,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":48449,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65272,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf533f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36462,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5340"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":88352,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5341"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9806,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5342"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8171,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5343"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":61122,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5344"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":52638,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5345"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":84432,"session":"kilo","subject":"HZWEH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf534f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25197,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5350"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9777,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5351"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":60947,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5352"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":40234,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5353"},"answer":"HJDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":151886,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5354"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13418,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5355"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35343,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5356"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":132509,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5357"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21589,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5358"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":51647,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5359"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14084,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf535a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10294,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf535b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32558,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf535c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42467,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf535d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":102021,"session":"lima","subject":"EJPRM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5367"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21341,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5368"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22744,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5369"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23184,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":41565,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":48363,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11594,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22681,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536e"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32343,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf536f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18039,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5370"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":36206,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5371"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9536,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5372"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8478,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5373"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32763,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5374"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31795,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5375"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":63960,"session":"lima","subject":"3H1U8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf537f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":9763,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5380"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15827,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5381"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26714,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5382"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":81446,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5383"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":57418,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5384"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12886,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5385"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25931,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5386"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":18783,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5387"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12228,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5388"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":29234,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5389"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10929,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf538a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11897,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf538b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33470,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf538c"},"answer":"EB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26783,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf538d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":31210,"session":"mike","subject":"967LR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5397"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13616,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5398"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8929,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5399"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12062,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11459,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82429,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6250,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26957,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37943,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf539f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24190,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":64010,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10442,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6458,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20985,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31059,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53a5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33127,"session":"mike","subject":"W8QKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53c7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32564,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":150151,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53c9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21994,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ca"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":32885,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53cb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":98540,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53cc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9245,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53cd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17609,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":23090,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53cf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":93347,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":33503,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7642,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":54209,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d3"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24189,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20027,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53d5"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37499,"session":"lima","subject":"MW3RC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53df"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":55480,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e0"},"answer":"J","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12540,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39884,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19541,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":115142,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8976,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21570,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46444,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16556,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":86807,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53e9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14786,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ea"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10223,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53eb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32652,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ec"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34218,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ed"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":66204,"session":"kilo","subject":"F98S2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53f7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18609,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19228,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53f9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28609,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53fa"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55371,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53fb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15680,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53fc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10422,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53fd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20553,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53fe"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":68097,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf53ff"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33921,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5400"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":55543,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5401"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13082,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5402"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":28464,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5403"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":48815,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5404"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34793,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5405"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38734,"session":"mike","subject":"CE2FW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf540f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":52233,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5410"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29352,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5411"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16869,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5412"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":45927,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5413"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":99016,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5414"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15025,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5415"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25799,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5416"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":21080,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5417"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":54481,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5418"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":60079,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5419"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16305,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf541a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16414,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf541b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39928,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf541c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":41114,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf541d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44769,"session":"mike","subject":"5QCE3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5427"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12966,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5428"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19392,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5429"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":37437,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542a"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":73858,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24254,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7326,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32231,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":61215,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf542f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16495,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5430"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":127528,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5431"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7037,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5432"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5945,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5433"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":37704,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5434"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":49431,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5435"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45703,"session":"mike","subject":"AKYQ8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf543f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13123,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5440"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14373,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5441"},"answer":"AUB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":33858,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5442"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":117868,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5443"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":199061,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5444"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6105,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5445"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":10723,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5446"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48468,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5447"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15000,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5448"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":95864,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5449"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12494,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf544a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6878,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf544b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31658,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf544c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17394,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf544d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":60173,"session":"mike","subject":"FL092"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5457"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19923,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5458"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14687,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5459"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25488,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545a"},"answer":"OU","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":70895,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":106414,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14275,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20720,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54698,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf545f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115-late","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22480,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5460"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":56690,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5461"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9133,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5462"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14146,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5463"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25962,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5464"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":40559,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5465"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"115-late","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":112095,"session":"mike","subject":"YC7SX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf546f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17484,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5470"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18514,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5471"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16247,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5472"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":53717,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5473"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":99942,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5474"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10886,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5475"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35052,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5476"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45541,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5477"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35538,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5478"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":49757,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5479"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19794,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf547a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16331,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf547b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33656,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf547c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31413,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf547d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57030,"session":"mike","subject":"3A2HT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5487"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":59586,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5488"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10072,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5489"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8468,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5240,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":11023,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10512,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15909,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30489,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf548f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14088,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5490"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6983,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5491"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5965,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5492"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5182,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5493"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26560,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5494"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9330,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5495"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10746,"session":"november","subject":"DFQLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf549f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26356,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10092,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a1"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11900,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44066,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":39006,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9837,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14047,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24438,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15970,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":24133,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54a9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7867,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54aa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5513,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13800,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ac"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33167,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21336,"session":"november","subject":"4P01U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54b7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15379,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54b8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6870,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54b9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12406,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ba"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11698,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54bb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":96228,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54bc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6812,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54bd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21884,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54be"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30342,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54bf"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20918,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":53675,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9623,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11901,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29678,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20655,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54c5"},"answer":"EB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":41804,"session":"november","subject":"K8DJ0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54cf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26363,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31107,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18460,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":102752,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82342,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12265,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":38957,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47769,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15011,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d8"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12813,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54d9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9983,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54da"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6798,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54db"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31213,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54dc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17249,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54dd"},"answer":"AD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21725,"session":"november","subject":"CKU4L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54e7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24150,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10629,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54e9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15295,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ea"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15241,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54eb"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":69458,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5742,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ed"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20912,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ee"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49027,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ef"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15901,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":50987,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14465,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7945,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28533,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31528,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54f5"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":30805,"session":"november","subject":"PLKGC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf54ff"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32734,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5500"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9520,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5501"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":38627,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5502"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9794,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5503"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":50653,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5504"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22981,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5505"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24903,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5506"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31367,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5507"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37048,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5508"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":42902,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5509"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13135,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf550a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":22985,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf550b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21540,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf550c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9092,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf550d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":61222,"session":"november","subject":"5ZEGW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5517"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22197,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5518"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16966,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5519"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":36630,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11813,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":41696,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13838,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30002,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":68530,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf551f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44031,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5520"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11013,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5521"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18649,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5522"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14393,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5523"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17888,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5524"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7523,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5525"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14758,"session":"november","subject":"B1Q98"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf552f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19128,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5530"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16813,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5531"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34285,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5532"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":48856,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5533"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":41009,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5534"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13507,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5535"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30663,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5536"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31270,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5537"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20710,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5538"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":46972,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5539"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15411,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf553a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11256,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf553b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":35014,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf553c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":48103,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf553d"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29062,"session":"november","subject":"55GO7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5547"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35791,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5548"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14203,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5549"},"answer":"OZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":82986,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44568,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554b"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":60009,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14683,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20258,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41207,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf554f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24806,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5550"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12439,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5551"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10618,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5552"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8776,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5553"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29217,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5554"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30602,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5555"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":32077,"session":"november","subject":"FK2HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf555f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":73748,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5560"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31264,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5561"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52482,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5562"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55651,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5563"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":19,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":542606,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5564"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20968,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5565"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":17,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":148066,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5566"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67204,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5567"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38354,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5568"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":151167,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5569"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18110,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf556a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14952,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf556b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":188328,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf556c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":101186,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf556d"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":147621,"session":"mike","subject":"BF0KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5577"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23322,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5578"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13512,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5579"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29743,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":28845,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":57557,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8714,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24609,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24427,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf557f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35734,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5580"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45020,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5581"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9366,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5582"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10628,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5583"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":64464,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5584"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34020,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5585"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":54777,"session":"november","subject":"53R9B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf558f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18778,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5590"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7321,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5591"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13913,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5592"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6395,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5593"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21556,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5594"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":35716,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5595"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28730,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5596"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50364,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5597"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":56348,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5598"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":4636,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5599"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10451,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf559a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5673,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf559b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12266,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf559c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8029,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf559d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16946,"session":"november","subject":"C78PK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55a7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19888,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55a8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22037,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55a9"},"answer":"XU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28773,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55aa"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":50719,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ab"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":119141,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7645,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ad"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22127,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ae"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28380,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55af"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30030,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52056,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7624,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15915,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":51959,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":45142,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55b5"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":69340,"session":"november","subject":"VB9NP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55bf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18134,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14768,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":69108,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":59369,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":128471,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14991,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25191,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33334,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21214,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48961,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55c9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9868,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ca"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11193,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55cb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32594,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55cc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":54861,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55cd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37575,"session":"november","subject":"TPGMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18387,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55d8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11896,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55d9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":44311,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55da"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":72686,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55db"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":124700,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8324,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55dd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26770,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55de"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49411,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13558,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41077,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6970,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10503,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25478,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30741,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55e5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27598,"session":"november","subject":"KYY96"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55ef"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44259,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8203,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22894,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":71640,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":131547,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8082,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20795,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":69211,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21796,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":74804,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55f9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12725,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55fa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9179,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55fb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":63838,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55fc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":44273,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf55fd"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":48702,"session":"november","subject":"YFWR3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5607"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":79667,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5608"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22765,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5609"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":52785,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22638,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":321918,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8662,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":63227,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":62909,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf560f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":39526,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5610"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":24512,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5611"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10991,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5612"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16626,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5613"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":61781,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5614"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":58465,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5615"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":32173,"session":"november","subject":"UV5LD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf561f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40802,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5620"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19961,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5621"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29777,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5622"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":93178,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5623"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":283787,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5624"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15688,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5625"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37101,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5626"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94929,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5627"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":55921,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5628"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":82942,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5629"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14606,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf562a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16058,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf562b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21096,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf562c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24597,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf562d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26698,"session":"november","subject":"ESMO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5637"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":75068,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5638"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15623,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5639"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":38666,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19304,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21470,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25212,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29291,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":64549,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf563f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":77942,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5640"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9948,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5641"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":20938,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5642"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12626,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5643"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29064,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5644"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":48506,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5645"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22754,"session":"november","subject":"2WQ0M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf564f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12491,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5650"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14373,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5651"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9186,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5652"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6917,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5653"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":7063,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5654"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":-5954,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5655"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25788,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5656"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43837,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5657"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23711,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5658"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6291,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5659"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6392,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf565a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6137,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf565b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31416,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf565c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14490,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf565d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9246,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"G72GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5667"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":42677,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5668"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27224,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5669"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39359,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":67313,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":80404,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9773,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16188,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60780,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf566f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31278,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5670"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":43107,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5671"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10800,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5672"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16001,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5673"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21823,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5674"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23098,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5675"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57366,"session":"alpha","subject":"UQWX4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf567f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":5095,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5680"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9580,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5681"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":6215,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5682"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6609,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5683"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":5516,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5684"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":4165,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5685"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14555,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5686"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":26798,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5687"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34440,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5688"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14688,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5689"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5650,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf568a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9468,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf568b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10526,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf568c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":4090,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf568d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11911,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"8MVD2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5697"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21581,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5698"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26557,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5699"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":43078,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569a"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":163990,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":109307,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15697,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":29560,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53745,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf569f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48146,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":77678,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8590,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19941,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":73297,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47558,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56a5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":96642,"session":"alpha","subject":"4RGO3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56c7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49866,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15071,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56c9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24689,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ca"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":63076,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56cb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":117842,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56cc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17983,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56cd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44189,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":74133,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56cf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27620,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":62335,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17717,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7450,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":72855,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21708,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56d5"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":55783,"session":"alpha","subject":"Z5Z7P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56df"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":39651,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e0"},"answer":"XE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27609,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e1"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27597,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12025,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e3"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":52919,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11359,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24673,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e6"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":18101,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48288,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12407,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56e9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9912,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ea"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10985,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56eb"},"answer":"GCO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27569,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10490,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ed"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":108954,"session":"bravo","subject":"YE3VQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56f7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37247,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56f8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7338,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56f9"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15926,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56fa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12975,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56fb"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":28346,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56fc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13451,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56fd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":49247,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56fe"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":45632,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf56ff"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18850,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5700"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41076,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5701"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10659,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5702"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6808,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5703"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46582,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5704"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19908,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5705"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":55950,"session":"bravo","subject":"DKL3R"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5727"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18289,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5728"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11694,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5729"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29660,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":113696,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572b"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":139274,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14262,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":51633,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44229,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf572f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16979,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5730"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14615,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5731"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9476,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5732"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10508,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5733"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":56749,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5734"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":68827,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5735"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80938,"session":"alpha","subject":"781AU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf573f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37525,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5740"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6976,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5741"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10034,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5742"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8410,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5743"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20514,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5744"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9159,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5745"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24935,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5746"},"answer":"IJEF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":7.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73064,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5747"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":49660,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5748"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6745,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5749"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17973,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf574a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6626,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf574b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22061,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf574c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7509,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf574d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11537,"session":"charlie","subject":"CC7G0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5757"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":68595,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5758"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14393,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5759"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10466,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14543,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":34389,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9581,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27399,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":31824,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf575f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42712,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5760"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8204,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5761"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10932,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5762"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9559,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5763"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19075,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5764"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9843,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5765"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17736,"session":"charlie","subject":"A9CZD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf576f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17150,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5770"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19151,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5771"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11837,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5772"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15550,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5773"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15543,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5774"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16292,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5775"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":41774,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5776"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":58193,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5777"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13456,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5778"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67124,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5779"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12563,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf577a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15449,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf577b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23933,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf577c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":54559,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf577d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":59052,"session":"bravo","subject":"DOQRP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5787"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12275,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5788"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10574,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5789"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":36484,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7659,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":146289,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9300,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21483,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51228,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf578f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14374,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5790"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":32304,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5791"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10055,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5792"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9200,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5793"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":74524,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5794"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39348,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5795"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":48909,"session":"charlie","subject":"Q8EDD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf579f"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29966,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a0"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23347,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31874,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a2"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8965,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a3"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":126678,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11789,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22391,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a6"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33256,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22157,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":70804,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57a9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8728,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57aa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12539,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49367,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ac"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18419,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50607,"session":"bravo","subject":"RGJZL"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57b7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30410,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57b8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46563,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57b9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":70472,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ba"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12816,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57bb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":54540,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57bc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16494,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57bd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28062,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57be"},"answer":"FGCO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41710,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57bf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35313,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8466,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7071,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7287,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23251,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6769,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57c5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20437,"session":"charlie","subject":"W7EBS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57cf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20331,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8592,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17955,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38042,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":114486,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8069,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27275,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47696,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24317,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":30728,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57d9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11238,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57da"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8228,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57db"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30374,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57dc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":29205,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57dd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33667,"session":"charlie","subject":"EGP0T"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57e7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26179,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17067,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57e9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17658,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ea"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":26778,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57eb"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":66932,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13424,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ed"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24354,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ee"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51774,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ef"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27711,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17773,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12324,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16469,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28841,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":32284,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57f5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33899,"session":"charlie","subject":"CK5DF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf57ff"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17959,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5800"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13242,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5801"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8685,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5802"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56046,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5803"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":95222,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5804"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12471,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5805"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25158,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5806"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":64558,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5807"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23711,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5808"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41822,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5809"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7066,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf580a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9042,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf580b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26113,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf580c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30286,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf580d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47246,"session":"charlie","subject":"9BBMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5817"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48803,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5818"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10563,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5819"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22924,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":51485,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":55391,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10517,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15710,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":88691,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf581f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34361,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5820"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44213,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5821"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9860,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5822"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17506,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5823"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36320,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5824"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22762,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5825"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":80900,"session":"charlie","subject":"UX4QZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf582f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70990,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5830"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":38664,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5831"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32361,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5832"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":8183,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5833"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12386,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5834"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9485,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5835"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25201,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5836"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60618,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5837"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35830,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5838"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12755,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5839"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10497,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf583a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13030,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf583b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14874,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf583c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11951,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf583d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14111,"session":"charlie","subject":"GQ35Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5847"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74261,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5848"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19550,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5849"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16765,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16689,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22755,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":52025,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28424,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85601,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf584f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":88032,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5850"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10862,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5851"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14284,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5852"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16906,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5853"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24502,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5854"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":17935,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5855"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14926,"session":"charlie","subject":"WKBNA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf585f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":42094,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5860"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28831,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5861"},"answer":"UE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27742,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5862"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":102206,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5863"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":101333,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5864"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11232,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5865"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30583,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5866"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34165,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5867"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":62113,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5868"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22499,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5869"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12090,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf586a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14133,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf586b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20408,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf586c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8823,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf586d"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":89734,"session":"charlie","subject":"F3GZE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5877"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27462,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5878"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11604,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5879"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28660,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587a"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58061,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":171227,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9577,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24297,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":68861,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf587f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18028,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5880"},"answer":"XZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":77717,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5881"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13486,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5882"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14811,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5883"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":37183,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5884"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":34078,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5885"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":70705,"session":"charlie","subject":"X9PTQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf588f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14084,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5890"},"answer":"KE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18750,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5891"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14136,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5892"},"answer":"HB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12795,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5893"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":10626,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5894"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19183,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5895"},"answer":"MX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44946,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5896"},"answer":"MO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30497,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5897"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":51728,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5898"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12626,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5899"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12904,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf589a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20947,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf589b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":40352,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf589c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12825,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf589d"},"answer":"EFZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12800,"session":"strategy-connecting","subject":"WQKT9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58a7"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41172,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58a8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30848,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58a9"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18426,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58aa"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17241,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ab"},"answer":"OHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32069,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21842,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ad"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22758,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ae"},"answer":"FO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":46480,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58af"},"answer":"JF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":124006,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41440,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10859,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":39663,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b3"},"answer":"LH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19301,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b4"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20215,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58b5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15298,"session":"strategy-satisficing","subject":"ZYASS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58bf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":18187,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25525,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c1"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20181,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c2"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18374,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":57540,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12647,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":50769,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":72145,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":43769,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":94216,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58c9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14782,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ca"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8621,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58cb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":64562,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58cc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":46483,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58cd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":66370,"session":"delta","subject":"5GELG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58d7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26422,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58d8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":52457,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58d9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25029,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58da"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56000,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58db"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":119669,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9315,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58dd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26580,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58de"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34824,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23381,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":39422,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9121,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8339,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":67129,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47008,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58e5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":73133,"session":"delta","subject":"FJV2A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58ef"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37619,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26582,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":57054,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":256100,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f3"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":271668,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9400,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39890,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65430,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44147,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":60809,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58f9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12773,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58fa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14837,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58fb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":112169,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58fc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":75099,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf58fd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":58584,"session":"charlie","subject":"J1JP6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5907"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28419,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5908"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":36440,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5909"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26375,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590a"},"answer":"OU","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":93751,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590b"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":149642,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16988,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17631,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50498,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf590f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23574,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5910"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":99492,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5911"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11961,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5912"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7752,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5913"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29410,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5914"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":57963,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5915"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":56722,"session":"delta","subject":"ELUPZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf591f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20033,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5920"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":52954,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5921"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25552,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5922"},"answer":"HB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12758,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5923"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21978,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5924"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17117,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5925"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34020,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5926"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35163,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5927"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13912,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5928"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5541,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5929"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6965,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf592a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8350,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf592b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9064,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf592c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6949,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf592d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11723,"session":"echo","subject":"38NFJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5937"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24038,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5938"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14944,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5939"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12446,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21297,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":51488,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14157,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22193,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":20697,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf593f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37659,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5940"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":5403,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5941"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13428,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5942"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7994,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5943"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16162,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5944"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6788,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5945"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10350,"session":"echo","subject":"QGQ61"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf594f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10053,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5950"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":31823,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5951"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10152,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5952"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":62869,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5953"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":38895,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5954"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9331,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5955"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20771,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5956"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24373,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5957"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14129,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5958"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41526,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5959"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10850,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf595a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8931,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf595b"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47430,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf595c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24490,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf595d"},"answer":"BM","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29435,"session":"echo","subject":"R06S6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5967"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":95264,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5968"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":122357,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5969"},"answer":"AIO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":73700,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596a"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":63926,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596b"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":84069,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8267,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18309,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34008,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf596f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18504,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5970"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15851,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5971"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11286,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5972"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7962,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5973"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30792,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5974"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14114,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5975"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39007,"session":"echo","subject":"808YR"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf597f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26807,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5980"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":41819,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5981"},"answer":"AO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29180,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5982"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":70109,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5983"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":169183,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5984"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8121,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5985"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39810,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5986"},"answer":"MC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35831,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5987"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35049,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5988"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":33723,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5989"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":32141,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf598a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7969,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf598b"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":49066,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf598c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":63697,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf598d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":59437,"session":"echo","subject":"VSHHA"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59af"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":36923,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":2376,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b1"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":6584,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":62847,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b3"},"answer":"ZFH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16129,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":68968,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b5"},"answer":"MK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":1967,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b6"},"answer":"AG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":13574,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b7"},"answer":"KD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":2962,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21917,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59b9"},"answer":"EMK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":3091,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ba"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8217,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59bb"},"answer":"MKD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":2846,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59bc"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8474,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59bd"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":1264,"session":"go1f","subject":"H2N27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59c7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":102636,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30829,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59c9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":43190,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ca"},"answer":"OUDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":83369,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59cb"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":129807,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59cc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":37559,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59cd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37869,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49070,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59cf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33682,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":123331,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21803,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":30171,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":69086,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":47743,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59d5"},"answer":"EB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"111","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":83324,"session":"foxtrot","subject":"6Y93F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59df"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29752,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10638,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11542,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6292,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":23387,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":35405,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36886,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54531,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31180,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12892,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59e9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10853,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ea"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10824,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59eb"},"answer":"HN","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13465,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9440,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ed"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14134,"session":"golf","subject":"H1RGT"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59f7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":82631,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59f8"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46721,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59f9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":108310,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59fa"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":116988,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59fb"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":206517,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59fc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15454,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59fd"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30654,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59fe"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57226,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf59ff"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23752,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a00"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":64816,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a01"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9553,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a02"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":21656,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a03"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":69369,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a04"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39952,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a05"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":7879,"session":"echo","subject":"MOWH2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a0f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":161362,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a10"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26143,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a11"},"answer":"AOU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":65299,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a12"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":98031,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a13"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":315445,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a14"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7117,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a15"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":71113,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a16"},"answer":"IJEFG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41276,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a17"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21762,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a18"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12291,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a19"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":20766,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a1a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17106,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a1b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11615,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a1c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9499,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a1d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16098,"session":"echo","subject":"FSWW4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a27"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49714,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a28"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":108440,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a29"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":27944,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11570,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18178,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14258,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36031,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2e"},"answer":"AGK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67292,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a2f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":32748,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a30"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8207,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a31"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12190,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a32"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9882,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a33"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9838,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a34"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8503,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a35"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":74609,"session":"golf","subject":"VT5BG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a3f"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":51939,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a40"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":32400,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a41"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":43537,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a42"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":56048,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a43"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":60599,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a44"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6570,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a45"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21557,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a46"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":66151,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a47"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20784,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a48"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":37663,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a49"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10666,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a4a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8535,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a4b"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24820,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a4c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16554,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a4d"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10408,"session":"golf","subject":"39GMD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a57"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":33814,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a58"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16889,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a59"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":3890,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5a"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16419,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5b"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32878,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10435,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28617,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5e"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38744,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a5f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20360,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a60"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15086,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a61"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9214,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a62"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4285,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a63"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":31866,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a64"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11475,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a65"},"answer":"BG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26408,"session":"hotel","subject":"YP2FK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a6f"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47965,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a70"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":76380,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a71"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31503,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a72"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":84146,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a73"},"answer":"FHJXK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75838,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a74"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10197,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a75"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14502,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a76"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":53595,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a77"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38650,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a78"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":49216,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a79"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9151,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a7a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11267,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a7b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36681,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a7c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30005,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a7d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":55052,"session":"golf","subject":"ZKB08"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5a9f"},"answer":"AI","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":61056,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16965,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28029,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":7968,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15482,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9763,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34879,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":15847,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa7"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23762,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14271,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aa9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16491,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aaa"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7929,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aab"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12745,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aac"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12170,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aad"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24779,"session":"hotel","subject":"D3LUH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ab7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70053,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ab8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8193,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ab9"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18791,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aba"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21919,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5abb"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":240581,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5abc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6482,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5abd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26785,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5abe"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":165697,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5abf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31217,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12508,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8247,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":3769,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac3"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":41500,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5971,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ac5"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24368,"session":"golf","subject":"DM4T0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5acf"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":43318,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13456,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":69907,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad2"},"answer":"HD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":109821,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad3"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":45179,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7471,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18966,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":86092,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17344,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48793,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ad9"},"answer":"MAGCKXOPLHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":13.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":51838,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ada"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9141,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5adb"},"answer":"GX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":46799,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5adc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":60663,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5add"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21582,"session":"golf","subject":"67NP2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ae7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":44790,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ae8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14934,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ae9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17515,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aea"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9635,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aeb"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":56608,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10554,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aed"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23321,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aee"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50258,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aef"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24306,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17234,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12602,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9352,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14377,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7552,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5af5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29487,"session":"hotel","subject":"8LK9M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5aff"},"answer":"AO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":39053,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b00"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16324,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b01"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12983,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b02"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10430,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b03"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21673,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b04"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8486,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b05"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14423,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b06"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":78355,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b07"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24999,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b08"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":55791,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b09"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13922,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b0a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8965,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b0b"},"answer":"LH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16980,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b0c"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7485,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b0d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":66302,"session":"hotel","subject":"OZV09"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b17"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":66132,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b18"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":124811,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b19"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17750,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15015,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1b"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":50223,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8123,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30573,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1e"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40701,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b1f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22232,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b20"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13000,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b21"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15943,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b22"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12800,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b23"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14631,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b24"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14071,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b25"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":35897,"session":"hotel","subject":"T5SHZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b2f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":96850,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b30"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20998,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b31"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21828,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b32"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16273,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b33"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16976,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b34"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15676,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b35"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21953,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b36"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55131,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b37"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":70860,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b38"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13610,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b39"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18213,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b3a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13357,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b3b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14860,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b3c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12841,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b3d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16906,"session":"hotel","subject":"QOJ6L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b47"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":12562,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b48"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11298,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b49"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10614,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":25092,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4b"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32324,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7052,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13664,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32842,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b4f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15096,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b50"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":18499,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b51"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13847,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b52"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4357,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b53"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21298,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b54"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":41205,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b55"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":29208,"session":"india","subject":"2S99A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b5f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50768,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b60"},"answer":"ZKUEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":9,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":117145,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b61"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":74836,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b62"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19968,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b63"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":148030,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b64"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7781,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b65"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17981,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b66"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34560,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b67"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16260,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b68"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16353,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b69"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11908,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b6a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5564,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b6b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27968,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b6c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21301,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b6d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":76587,"session":"hotel","subject":"AFQCB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b77"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20961,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b78"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14026,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b79"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20953,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7a"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":31988,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7b"},"answer":"AO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":37559,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12965,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20757,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7e"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47546,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b7f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14542,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b80"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45557,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b81"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12121,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b82"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9547,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b83"},"answer":"FM","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23424,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b84"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":25338,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5b85"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":24594,"session":"india","subject":"CMMGH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ba7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28904,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ba8"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":33290,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ba9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29961,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5baa"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":50198,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bab"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":130962,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10110,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bad"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17604,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bae"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54946,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5baf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29864,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":43181,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10447,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8009,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23384,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35897,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bb5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":49022,"session":"india","subject":"Q3JLW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bbf"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":80319,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13505,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16600,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13425,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":67714,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22650,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":42980,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":64159,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26950,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12000,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bc9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11287,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bca"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11953,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bcb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24320,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bcc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8750,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bcd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":32171,"session":"juliet","subject":"ZY4DY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bd7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17989,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bd8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14425,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bd9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16947,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bda"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":76038,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bdb"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":117553,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bdc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12983,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bdd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23706,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bde"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":60126,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bdf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":86061,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17186,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18759,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6516,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13550,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8534,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5be5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12176,"session":"juliet","subject":"OU2PE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bef"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16760,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8895,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24377,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44343,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf3"},"answer":"IH","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":64277,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8384,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16401,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf6"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25135,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14105,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf8"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":37895,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bf9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9457,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bfa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9225,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bfb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":5.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":43713,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bfc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":39835,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5bfd"},"answer":"EFB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44035,"session":"india","subject":"C30CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c07"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46346,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c08"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20116,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c09"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21808,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":7.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":54025,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":59746,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8471,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31559,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40596,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c0f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35087,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c10"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":58456,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c11"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8680,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c12"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6096,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c13"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29276,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c14"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11067,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c15"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38609,"session":"juliet","subject":"BEGT5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c1f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":62663,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c20"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11218,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c21"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13338,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c22"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":18325,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c23"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":21274,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c24"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10097,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c25"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30516,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c26"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48146,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c27"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31933,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c28"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9168,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c29"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":24451,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c2a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14559,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c2b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26571,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c2c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11997,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c2d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21573,"session":"juliet","subject":"JVUC6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c37"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":38065,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c38"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8021,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c39"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22309,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19865,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":73678,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8442,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20761,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29901,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c3f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19099,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c40"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":35194,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c41"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10420,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c42"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9577,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c43"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24572,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c44"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36779,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c45"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":30710,"session":"juliet","subject":"2KONX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c67"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":53511,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c68"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8296,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c69"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12568,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9402,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":38958,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9887,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19045,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":52765,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c6f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60605,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c70"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7555,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c71"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9632,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c72"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8806,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c73"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10209,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c74"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5367,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c75"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":7961,"session":"juliet","subject":"0QG7J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c7f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47123,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c80"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11183,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c81"},"answer":"AOU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28030,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c82"},"answer":"KD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17298,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c83"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":336033,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c84"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9079,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c85"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":43025,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c86"},"answer":"IJEOHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":8.5,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":69928,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c87"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":51556,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c88"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":67791,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c89"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19424,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c8a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6115,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c8b"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":66847,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c8c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":42435,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c8d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"121","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":2,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":45992,"session":"hotel","subject":"G443Q"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c97"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54744,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c98"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30931,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c99"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26492,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":70757,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":88814,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10344,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25216,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38320,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5c9f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":36221,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":77579,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16090,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11646,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":27987,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36299,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ca5"},"answer":"EFX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":99144,"session":"juliet","subject":"E5L6P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5caf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23858,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11073,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":47901,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":19254,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":85875,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11106,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":32651,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb6"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":136934,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":50819,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":75265,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cb9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9727,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cba"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8864,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cbb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15463,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cbc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28480,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cbd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":101912,"session":"juliet","subject":"Q0QHK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cc7"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":87362,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cc8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":73014,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cc9"},"answer":"AIOZFHUEGB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":10,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":65503,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cca"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":29093,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ccb"},"answer":"OHJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20436,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ccc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20326,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ccd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":79788,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":107829,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ccf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28690,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd0"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22786,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19723,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":26260,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd3"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":37951,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd4"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":32710,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cd5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33091,"session":"juliet","subject":"2LZ7W"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cdf"},"answer":"AF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":124691,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":54993,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce1"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":79477,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce2"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":65993,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce3"},"answer":"UB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":61306,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18754,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25963,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55209,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce7"},"answer":"IF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":64766,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce8"},"answer":"JBXZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41279,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ce9"},"answer":"JFBX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21002,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cea"},"answer":"JBXO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":40135,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ceb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":48534,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cec"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":33186,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ced"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":77406,"session":"juliet","subject":"PRRKJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cf7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17977,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cf8"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8450,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cf9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10365,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cfa"},"answer":"JD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46864,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cfb"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":25998,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cfc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9473,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cfd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20225,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cfe"},"answer":"M","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":14591,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5cff"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":22944,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d00"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9102,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d01"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13080,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d02"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11849,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d03"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25398,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d04"},"answer":"L","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":14085,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d05"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":47277,"session":"oscar","subject":"53WYU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d0f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23147,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d10"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9185,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d11"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":51068,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d12"},"answer":"CAUB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":80846,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d13"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":38590,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d14"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":30951,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d15"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12210,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d16"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":62350,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d17"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19955,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d18"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":47889,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d19"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10848,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d1a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6683,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d1b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10524,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d1c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":56402,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d1d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":69652,"session":"oscar","subject":"FR69M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d27"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15786,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d28"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":24785,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d29"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":5.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26568,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2a"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":44245,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":58831,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":17788,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":6.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":38871,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":28366,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d2f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14814,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d30"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25985,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d31"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16646,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d32"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11004,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d33"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26968,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d34"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24598,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d35"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":60042,"session":"oscar","subject":"AZKMW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d57"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19668,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d58"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7511,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d59"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24784,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":47635,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118834,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10974,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22527,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56702,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d5f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":55278,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d60"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":44602,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d61"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11126,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d62"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8805,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d63"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25214,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d64"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":35374,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d65"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":37299,"session":"oscar","subject":"K7JVY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d6f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40692,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d70"},"answer":"IX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":65444,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d71"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16568,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d72"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11659,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d73"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":54370,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d74"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":56354,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d75"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28263,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d76"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43514,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d77"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":41636,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d78"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23956,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d79"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9262,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d7a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10410,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d7b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14936,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d7c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8246,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d7d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28033,"session":"oscar","subject":"FUXZY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d87"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":13826,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d88"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13036,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d89"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16770,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":50478,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82059,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10864,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34748,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51402,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d8f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26547,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d90"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":43439,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d91"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10755,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d92"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16425,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d93"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":19111,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d94"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":44870,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d95"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":44679,"session":"oscar","subject":"8GUB2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5d9f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37636,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9995,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21823,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12722,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":63723,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9516,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22557,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da6"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":89798,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19810,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da8"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":95757,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5da9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11126,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5daa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13334,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18215,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dac"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":24948,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":60755,"session":"papa","subject":"MD6NK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dcf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":26220,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15268,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":42590,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":81555,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd3"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":92419,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11822,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21178,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":41091,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":50613,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":84263,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dd9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11229,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dda"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15197,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ddb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39885,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ddc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":68877,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ddd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":43552,"session":"oscar","subject":"RRF03"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5de7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":39809,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5de8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15064,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5de9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14174,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dea"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":97317,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5deb"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":203468,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9525,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ded"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21921,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dee"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39241,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5def"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":62687,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":73630,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15204,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10501,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18713,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":48926,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5df5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":73457,"session":"oscar","subject":"TGOML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5dff"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16337,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e00"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13509,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e01"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12341,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e02"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13101,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e03"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77720,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e04"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8498,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e05"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19191,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e06"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39590,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e07"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12515,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e08"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":31229,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e09"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12138,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e0a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6317,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e0b"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":35905,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e0c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19486,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e0d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":22960,"session":"oscar","subject":"1N858"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e17"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27542,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e18"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16058,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e19"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":47752,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39575,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":63842,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8370,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":62285,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1e"},"answer":"MGC","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":42641,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e1f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":25338,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e20"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":29881,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e21"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15555,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e22"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10998,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e23"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50411,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e24"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":50878,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e25"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":71543,"session":"papa","subject":"Y9NLY"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e2f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":62776,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e30"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":91002,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e31"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22127,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e32"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":69260,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e33"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118034,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e34"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16743,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e35"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35523,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e36"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47366,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e37"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":23582,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e38"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":81056,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e39"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9825,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e3a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9443,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e3b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":57821,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e3c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":28820,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e3d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":71914,"session":"quebec","subject":"EPDQP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e47"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":41217,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e48"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17226,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e49"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11509,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9108,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":59385,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8455,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16761,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":32147,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e4f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19814,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e50"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":19058,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e51"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15048,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e52"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9392,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e53"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34685,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e54"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31692,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e55"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46777,"session":"romeo","subject":"F92ER"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e5f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50627,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e60"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27379,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e61"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":260014,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e62"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":132956,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e63"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":182342,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e64"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13168,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e65"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":46823,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e66"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":54811,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e67"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27654,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e68"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52285,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e69"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14581,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e6a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12082,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e6b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30749,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e6c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23806,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e6d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":76608,"session":"papa","subject":"0YZ27"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e77"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":7787,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e78"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10520,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e79"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9838,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7a"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9851,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13185,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25728,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7d"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18516,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":25683,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e7f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14279,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e80"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":24070,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e81"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7905,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e82"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7647,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e83"},"answer":"CO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":25287,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e84"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6210,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e85"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":40822,"session":"romeo","subject":"8TCFP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e8f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35958,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e90"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14752,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e91"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21677,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e92"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":78941,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e93"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":126515,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e94"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114\n114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20508,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e95"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25333,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e96"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":26987,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e97"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16191,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e98"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":72061,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e99"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14650,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e9a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13404,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e9b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21453,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e9c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":53240,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5e9d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114\n114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":49567,"session":"papa","subject":"BWVFU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ea7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":14150,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ea8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20035,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ea9"},"answer":"AIOZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":4.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":40272,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eaa"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11169,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eab"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":79104,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8826,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ead"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31771,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eae"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49973,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eaf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44628,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":98234,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10846,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7793,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":43237,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":78663,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eb5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":93006,"session":"papa","subject":"NVKL3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ebf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":17719,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11799,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21331,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":66379,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec3"},"answer":"OF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":77075,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8836,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15991,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":103272,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16513,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec8"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":124366,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ec9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9178,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eca"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8820,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ecb"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47471,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ecc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":53331,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ecd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":48186,"session":"papa","subject":"G8P43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5eef"},"answer":"CAUB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":51956,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef0"},"answer":"JK","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21199,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef1"},"answer":"AOJUB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":5.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21085,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef2"},"answer":"DEGB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16683,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef3"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16028,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":28492,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":44931,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef6"},"answer":"IJEFM","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":5.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43807,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15691,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef8"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12553,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ef9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9865,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5efa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10204,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5efb"},"answer":"PL","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26233,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5efc"},"answer":"ON","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":27598,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5efd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17253,"session":"tango","subject":"93XU7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f07"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":89370,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f08"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":74230,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f09"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17888,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0a"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38291,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":69849,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7375,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20192,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":36728,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f0f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16576,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f10"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15662,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f11"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7640,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f12"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6491,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f13"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20451,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f14"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21656,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f15"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23645,"session":"romeo","subject":"XD9UF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f37"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":47588,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f38"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":120691,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f39"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16939,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11835,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72089,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21761,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":19428,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":62233,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f3f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38982,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f40"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":12353,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f41"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10589,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f42"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12300,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f43"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9667,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f44"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9029,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f45"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":26705,"session":"sierra","subject":"FA2ZF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f4f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":22190,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f50"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":18717,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f51"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23225,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f52"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13803,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f53"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":35878,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f54"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13297,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f55"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20129,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f56"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73822,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f57"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31946,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f58"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":41321,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f59"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14739,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f5a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11125,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f5b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20881,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f5c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16061,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f5d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":34626,"session":"tango","subject":"DK1EM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f67"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":10793,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f68"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8540,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f69"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":31979,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":63075,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":72905,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5867,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23391,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39189,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f6f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":14863,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f70"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":4832,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f71"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9577,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f72"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9916,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f73"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":50177,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f74"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20589,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f75"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":32853,"session":"sierra","subject":"4LZ8B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f7f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":48589,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f80"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9661,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f81"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":56693,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f82"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":72107,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f83"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":73135,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f84"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7616,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f85"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21159,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f86"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":7,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":128177,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f87"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":40956,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f88"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":23783,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f89"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12380,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f8a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":41646,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f8b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17655,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f8c"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30954,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f8d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":28166,"session":"tango","subject":"8FE87"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f97"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16206,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f98"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17679,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f99"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":41898,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9a"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17967,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":12365,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":28160,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":13876,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":48773,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5f9f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":16734,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa0"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":37481,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":23745,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5281,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa3"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":48159,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa4"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":58103,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fa5"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11507,"session":"uniform","subject":"LW2XG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5faf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31757,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11372,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18426,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":73513,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb3"},"answer":"FU","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91421,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19676,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18240,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":66252,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":132909,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45717,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fb9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8650,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fba"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13359,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fbb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20148,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fbc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":53707,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fbd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":38186,"session":"romeo","subject":"7H6QC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fc7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32900,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fc8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":84567,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fc9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":40326,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fca"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":74595,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fcb"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75957,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fcc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11567,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fcd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25422,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fce"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":7.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":88221,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fcf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38369,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":38197,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12771,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":14379,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":35140,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":21834,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fd5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46570,"session":"sierra","subject":"9PKA7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fdf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":74003,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11653,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":48907,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe2"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":24475,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":59138,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11033,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18308,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":69489,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe7"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18104,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17230,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fe9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7038,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fea"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11194,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5feb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28919,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30919,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fed"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21449,"session":"uniform","subject":"HPKMO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ff7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19867,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ff8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15831,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ff9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":54272,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ffa"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":101445,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ffb"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":141398,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ffc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25341,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ffd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":61265,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5ffe"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":59774,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf5fff"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":98142,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6000"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":81453,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6001"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19555,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6002"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":26033,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6003"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":45225,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6004"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":58087,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6005"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":87146,"session":"uniform","subject":"03QKB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf600f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37763,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6010"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":30687,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6011"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21753,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6012"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":15927,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6013"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":181635,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6014"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12627,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6015"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":14542,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6016"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47471,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6017"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35128,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6018"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":78545,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6019"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9539,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf601a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12482,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf601b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":39981,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf601c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":63448,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf601d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":51957,"session":"tango","subject":"CSU5Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6027"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":34149,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6028"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14773,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6029"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":80258,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602a"},"answer":"HB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":8.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":236900,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602b"},"answer":"FDGB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":132965,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7506,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602d"},"answer":"IJXOZN","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":7,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":43265,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":77777,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf602f"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30611,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6030"},"answer":"BX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22202,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6031"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6422,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6032"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":28377,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6033"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32645,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6034"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":76244,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6035"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":4,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":75288,"session":"tango","subject":"SQ6AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6057"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":11112,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6058"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12999,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6059"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24744,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":74744,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":111057,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8878,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":17048,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37751,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf605f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":34019,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6060"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":45263,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6061"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9213,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6062"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4662,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6063"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":63513,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6064"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30124,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6065"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":27054,"session":"uniform","subject":"XQ4O8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf606f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28493,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6070"},"answer":"K","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9652,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6071"},"answer":"AH","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":32251,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6072"},"answer":"H","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":55576,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6073"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":169744,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6074"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":36631,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6075"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":64310,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6076"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43506,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6077"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":100282,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6078"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6277,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6079"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10552,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf607a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9424,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf607b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17508,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf607c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5728,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf607d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16002,"session":"tango","subject":"0CR6Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6087"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":92446,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6088"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20336,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6089"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":117659,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39826,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":82976,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8883,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21301,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35645,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf608f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24361,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6090"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20997,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6091"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13620,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6092"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12302,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6093"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":30622,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6094"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":19940,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6095"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50330,"session":"victor","subject":"DZD6F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf609f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":8364,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":28979,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12040,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":38989,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":55844,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8024,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":23687,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":38172,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18864,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":20079,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60a9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12296,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60aa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10743,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":40650,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ac"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":22874,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":31238,"session":"whiskey","subject":"ZAOCZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60b7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":60021,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60b8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8798,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60b9"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13059,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ba"},"answer":"","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":46325,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60bb"},"answer":"U","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":104181,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60bc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":20290,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60bd"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":24301,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60be"},"answer":"E","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47201,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60bf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20767,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":131687,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":20258,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13374,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":47554,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":30591,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60c5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Triangular-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"113","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":42094,"session":"tango","subject":"X2QZK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60cf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":19626,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13163,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22309,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":70831,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d3"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":69424,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8023,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16274,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43340,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47261,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":36784,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60d9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11216,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60da"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10942,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60db"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":34459,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60dc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":32723,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60dd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":39441,"session":"whiskey","subject":"2OEC4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60e7"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":91108,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60e8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":46781,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60e9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15629,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ea"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10835,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60eb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32186,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21981,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ed"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":25225,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ee"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":55031,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ef"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":52129,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14196,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10393,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7650,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":7,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33850,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9708,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60f5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15655,"session":"whiskey","subject":"1Z2H9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf60ff"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25239,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6100"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20843,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6101"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22079,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6102"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39966,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6103"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":112755,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6104"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8852,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6105"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":42136,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6106"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40991,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6107"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28273,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6108"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8060,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6109"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10420,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf610a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11674,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf610b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":75968,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf610c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":36143,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf610d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":49387,"session":"whiskey","subject":"QGUGU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6117"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":45883,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6118"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":14566,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6119"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17131,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10016,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":20729,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10138,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28604,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":30793,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf611f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":37732,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6120"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11817,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6121"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11649,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6122"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10972,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6123"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11295,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6124"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26116,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6125"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12547,"session":"xray","subject":"7BW1K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf612f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25898,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6130"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25354,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6131"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":19403,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6132"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58529,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6133"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":90781,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6134"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9786,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6135"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31029,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6136"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85823,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6137"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":48390,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6138"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":131369,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6139"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14549,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf613a"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":3,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16620,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf613b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":68343,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf613c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":75316,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf613d"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":0,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":50038,"session":"victor","subject":"A9C1X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6147"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30133,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6148"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":41440,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6149"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18747,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":121708,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":118108,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16708,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":59504,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":73763,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf614f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38000,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6150"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":22552,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6151"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11658,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6152"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":33046,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6153"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2.5,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":22907,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6154"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":1,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15566,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6155"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YInside","clicks":2,"condition":"114","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14883,"session":"victor","subject":"LBHUP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf615f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28421,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6160"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12144,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6161"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":22984,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6162"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":21249,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6163"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":96039,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6164"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15374,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6165"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34500,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6166"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":101506,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6167"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35083,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6168"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":57849,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6169"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14684,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf616a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":36229,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf616b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":60735,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf616c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":53384,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf616d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":60815,"session":"whiskey","subject":"MWJFN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6177"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32277,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6178"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12232,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6179"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12707,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":58908,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617b"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":104839,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8078,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15421,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617e"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":43445,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf617f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":15656,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6180"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":48167,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6181"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11517,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6182"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8189,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6183"},"answer":"EX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15054,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6184"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":26332,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6185"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":46772,"session":"whiskey","subject":"9BS72"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf618f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15942,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6190"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26324,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6191"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":13250,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6192"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9015,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6193"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":34840,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6194"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":36807,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6195"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28167,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6196"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":49933,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6197"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30546,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6198"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15470,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6199"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7811,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf619a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8521,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf619b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13240,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf619c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6929,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf619d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21166,"session":"xray","subject":"202VN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61a7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":46091,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61a8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9820,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61a9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":10884,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61aa"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12481,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ab"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":34405,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14157,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ad"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20612,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ae"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":35400,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61af"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27278,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7115,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11659,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6671,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12344,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5537,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61b5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23428,"session":"xray","subject":"HW2SN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61bf"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":40330,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13617,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9281,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5988,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":14948,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":58244,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c5"},"answer":"FZ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27349,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":47613,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31857,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7177,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61c9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":5694,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ca"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6142,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61cb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":7668,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61cc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8005,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61cd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":20040,"session":"xray","subject":"1HR1L"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61d7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23576,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61d8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":9455,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61d9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15124,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61da"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6836,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61db"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":19849,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10423,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61dd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22071,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61de"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":51967,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":29390,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14072,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8837,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15124,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10294,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6175,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61e5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":12688,"session":"xray","subject":"DJRH1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61ef"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31434,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f0"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":26066,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11869,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14411,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29965,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9513,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":22542,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37053,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":53430,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11144,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61f9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11310,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61fa"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7560,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61fb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13280,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61fc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8286,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf61fd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10229,"session":"xray","subject":"JPN18"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6207"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":85222,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6208"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":42392,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6209"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28432,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620a"},"answer":"UDE","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":175255,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":182052,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":19164,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620d"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":27310,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":67594,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf620f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":20479,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6210"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":52907,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6211"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":19255,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6212"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":89971,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6213"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":28849,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6214"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":49466,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6215"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XFull-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"115","correct":0,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57313,"session":"uniform","subject":"PWFDZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6237"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32416,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6238"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13723,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6239"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15248,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10733,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16798,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":30926,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28377,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24423,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf623f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":74682,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6240"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9923,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6241"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12874,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6242"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7921,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6243"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18412,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6244"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8588,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6245"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10254,"session":"xray","subject":"AG2V3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6267"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29801,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6268"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":11850,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6269"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":30285,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626a"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39539,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":53861,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":22796,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31758,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":56325,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf626f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28756,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6270"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":83477,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6271"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17329,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6272"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9891,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6273"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":36752,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6274"},"answer":"BO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":51386,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6275"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":51393,"session":"xray","subject":"41Y1H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf627f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":37216,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6280"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":16224,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6281"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21592,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6282"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17285,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6283"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":75846,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6284"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":10163,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6285"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":40399,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6286"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":71644,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6287"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":77495,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6288"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13069,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6289"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11769,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf628a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":16105,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf628b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15150,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf628c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7551,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf628d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":49410,"session":"xray","subject":"EPA4S"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6297"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30166,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6298"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":65641,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6299"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":36297,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":22603,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":29206,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":15272,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":40815,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39195,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf629f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":27172,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10241,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":23335,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12558,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26678,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8260,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62a5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":14083,"session":"xray","subject":"EER58"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62af"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20259,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":101297,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20850,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27279,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":90111,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18850,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":61510,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":102646,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":24697,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14947,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62b9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13344,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ba"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11601,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62bb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17694,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62bc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":13711,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62bd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23716,"session":"xray","subject":"X9225"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62c7"},"answer":"CD","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":32848,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62c8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":34113,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62c9"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":9518,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ca"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10233,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62cb"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":44264,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62cc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5448,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62cd"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35103,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ce"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":11333,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62cf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":13678,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d0"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8924,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6707,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":5883,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d3"},"answer":"CX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15858,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d4"},"answer":"D","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16538,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62d5"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":4677,"session":"yankee","subject":"9TE89"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62df"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":97683,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":15819,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":25056,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16344,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32759,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18985,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":35607,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":57760,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":32508,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11218,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62e9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":15247,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ea"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11758,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62eb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14422,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12419,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ed"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25252,"session":"xray","subject":"F9531"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62f7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24492,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62f8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":43590,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62f9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":100588,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62fa"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":28506,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62fb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26376,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62fc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":18064,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62fd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":82873,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62fe"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":94327,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf62ff"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":77373,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6300"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":28306,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6301"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":21933,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6302"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":20968,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6303"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":16913,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6304"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10188,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6305"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9491,"session":"xray","subject":"5KWEX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf630f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16687,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6310"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13047,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6311"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":15118,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6312"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":30725,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6313"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":35082,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6314"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6948,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6315"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26383,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6316"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44633,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6317"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12219,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6318"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":24728,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6319"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12559,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf631a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4577,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf631b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21285,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf631c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":20350,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf631d"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":10135,"session":"yankee","subject":"ZEPVG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6327"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":39284,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6328"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6914,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6329"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14738,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":23949,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24116,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":5278,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":34067,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632e"},"answer":"AK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":39912,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf632f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":33020,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6330"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8054,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6331"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8493,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6332"},"answer":"GP","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7369,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6333"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13364,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6334"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6875,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6335"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11586,"session":"yankee","subject":"MCVE6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf633f"},"answer":"CF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":21145,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6340"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25315,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6341"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20288,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6342"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16742,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6343"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":49942,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6344"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16448,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6345"},"answer":"CH","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":12815,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6346"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29779,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6347"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30626,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6348"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10435,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6349"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":6910,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf634a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9128,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf634b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":9773,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf634c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8825,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf634d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15699,"session":"yankee","subject":"8EQOW"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6357"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49580,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6358"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12321,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6359"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":20731,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":14367,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":22232,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13616,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":20260,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37516,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf635f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":19110,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6360"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16571,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6361"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13551,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6362"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11532,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6363"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15961,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6364"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5359,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6365"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9521,"session":"yankee","subject":"BK993"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf636f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":145677,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6370"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":45532,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6371"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34980,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6372"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":23702,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6373"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":91680,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6374"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":31331,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6375"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":82003,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6376"},"answer":"C","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":159262,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6377"},"answer":"IE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":68784,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6378"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17744,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6379"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":29997,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf637a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12110,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf637b"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":32253,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf637c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":10146,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf637d"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":48458,"session":"xray","subject":"CE3B9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6387"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":27238,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6388"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":59253,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6389"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":28471,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":12537,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":30965,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":24674,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":33372,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":85240,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf638f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30248,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6390"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":17480,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6391"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10127,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6392"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18730,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6393"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":20185,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6394"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18797,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6395"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":15475,"session":"xray","subject":"FBPNS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf639f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":15636,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21589,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23642,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a2"},"answer":"XU","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17691,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":26913,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8573,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18413,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a6"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":34535,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":18080,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a8"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":25859,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63a9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10055,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63aa"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7867,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ab"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29099,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ac"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":45037,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ad"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":58467,"session":"yankee","subject":"S6D2F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63b7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":55647,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63b8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":40666,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63b9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14160,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ba"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16698,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63bb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":28282,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63bc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":43279,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63bd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":77450,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63be"},"answer":"IEF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":74815,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63bf"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":60922,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9739,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11508,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7904,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24255,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7294,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63c5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16740,"session":"yankee","subject":"13RHM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63cf"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":35430,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":10523,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12428,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16970,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":15459,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13076,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":28114,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":95873,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":38010,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9704,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63d9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":13755,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63da"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":18575,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63db"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11974,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63dc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7124,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63dd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":21616,"session":"yankee","subject":"6GNVQ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63e7"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31232,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":25803,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63e9"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":66172,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ea"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":27963,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63eb"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":23046,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ec"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12933,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ed"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":36591,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ee"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":103013,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ef"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0.5,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":44554,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":21724,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11390,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8013,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":13248,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7112,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63f5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":13585,"session":"yankee","subject":"TZYD4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf63ff"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":50254,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6400"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7836,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6401"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":11023,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6402"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10808,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6403"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16777,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6404"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6013,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6405"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":31961,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6406"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":91924,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6407"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":45863,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6408"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":11537,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6409"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7300,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf640a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6159,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf640b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11957,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf640c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9780,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf640d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":25309,"session":"yankee","subject":"1N65C"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6417"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":25737,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6418"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20274,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6419"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14156,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":39679,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641b"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":68712,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":16424,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311\n311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":71197,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641e"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":65211,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf641f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":17919,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6420"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":81304,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6421"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14020,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6422"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":40875,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6423"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":26986,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6424"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":12945,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6425"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311\n311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":57292,"session":"yankee","subject":"74OF5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf642f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":4672,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6430"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6402,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6431"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":8888,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6432"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":5464,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6433"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":6168,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6434"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9055,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6435"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":18544,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6436"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":12670,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6437"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10801,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6438"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":4927,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6439"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10551,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf643a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":8844,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf643b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17198,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf643c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":5013,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf643d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":8662,"session":"yankee","subject":"G27Q3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf645f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":70003,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6460"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":21532,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6461"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":14921,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6462"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16254,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6463"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":33956,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6464"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":9380,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6465"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":39093,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6466"},"answer":"IJEFGCOHZND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":11,"condition":"311","correct":0,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":104844,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6467"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":35788,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6468"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9695,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6469"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8303,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf646a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6647,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf646b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":15294,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf646c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7856,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf646d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11009,"session":"yankee","subject":"CKDM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6477"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23937,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6478"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":7307,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6479"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":16478,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":6742,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13245,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21919,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30299,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":61168,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf647f"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":81238,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6480"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":6066,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6481"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":7889,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6482"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":9964,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6483"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11448,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6484"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":7204,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6485"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":11002,"session":"zulu","subject":"06217"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf648f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":29062,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6490"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17930,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6491"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":17083,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6492"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":17028,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6493"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":16850,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6494"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21311,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6495"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30666,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6496"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50725,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6497"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":26135,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6498"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10221,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6499"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":18443,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf649a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":17074,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf649b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14550,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf649c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":15686,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf649d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"311","correct":1,"explicit":3,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17067,"session":"yankee","subject":"JYGX2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64a7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":20998,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64a8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":20900,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64a9"},"answer":"FUE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":39002,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64aa"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":77832,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ab"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":18745,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ac"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11068,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ad"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26628,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ae"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":33289,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64af"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":31894,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":10163,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16275,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12282,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":11481,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6351,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64b5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":16034,"session":"zulu","subject":"MUULG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64bf"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":30981,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":8944,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c1"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26802,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":11566,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":24612,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":56474,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26328,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c6"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40197,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":75067,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":8957,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64c9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11901,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ca"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":6232,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64cb"},"answer":"JA","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":10801,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64cc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8276,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64cd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":9736,"session":"zulu","subject":"K0CNH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64d7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31275,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64d8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":23478,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64d9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23291,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64da"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":13998,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64db"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32908,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64dc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":7480,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64dd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":30080,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64de"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":40401,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64df"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":28568,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9859,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8064,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11264,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":21214,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":11443,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64e5"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":23537,"session":"zulu","subject":"VHSFM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64ef"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":16966,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":6363,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f1"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":49267,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f2"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16683,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":38935,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":21576,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f5"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":15559,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f6"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":29858,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":10605,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f8"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7191,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64f9"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":8372,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64fa"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":4200,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64fb"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":42966,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64fc"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":18658,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf64fd"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":34987,"session":"zulu","subject":"QCQYM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6507"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28487,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6508"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12559,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6509"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":12527,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650a"},"answer":"HJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":25534,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":65720,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":8837,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":63919,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":37380,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf650f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":25427,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6510"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":16706,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6511"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":9530,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6512"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19480,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6513"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":23372,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6514"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8221,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6515"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18702,"session":"zulu","subject":"8182H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf651f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":24354,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6520"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":22662,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6521"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":24028,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6522"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":41325,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6523"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":119735,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6524"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":13236,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6525"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":21794,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6526"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":24437,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6527"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":32358,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6528"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":32894,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6529"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":16478,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf652a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":12173,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf652b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":29198,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf652c"},"answer":"","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":0,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":16530,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf652d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33569,"session":"zulu","subject":"TCTCN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6537"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":53344,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6538"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":38470,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6539"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":23593,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653a"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":9962,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653b"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":13385,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":14426,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653d"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37312,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653e"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":89417,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf653f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":84282,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6540"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9111,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6541"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11942,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6542"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10152,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6543"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":24386,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6544"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9172,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6545"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":19598,"session":"zulu","subject":"CWE2H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf654f"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":31128,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6550"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":17491,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6551"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":18972,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6552"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":10808,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6553"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":32763,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6554"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":42400,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6555"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":69059,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6556"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":126633,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6557"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":47144,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6558"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":9253,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6559"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":14383,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf655a"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10223,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf655b"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":14900,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf655c"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":9464,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf655d"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18441,"session":"zulu","subject":"TTCWS"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6567"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":49620,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6568"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":29224,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6569"},"answer":"IO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":40535,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656a"},"answer":"DE","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":28456,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656b"},"answer":"HK","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":4.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":83002,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":25104,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656d"},"answer":"ND","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":26571,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656e"},"answer":"J","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":76876,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf656f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":12775,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6570"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":13846,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6571"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":17425,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6572"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":13594,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6573"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":135297,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6574"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":45261,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6575"},"answer":"MG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":62958,"session":"zulu","subject":"VVH1B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf657f"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":23923,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6580"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":19761,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6581"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":26064,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6582"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":76250,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6583"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":84187,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6584"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":11384,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6585"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":37694,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6586"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":44005,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6587"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":21168,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6588"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":39601,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6589"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11784,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf658a"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":15048,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf658b"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":33029,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf658c"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":23635,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf658d"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":131482,"session":"zulu","subject":"Z5GWP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6597"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":54083,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6598"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":12731,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf6599"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":51408,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659a"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":77493,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659b"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":123882,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659c"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12711,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659d"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":16891,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659e"},"answer":"IJ","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":20616,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf659f"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":30416,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a0"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":43094,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a1"},"answer":"FB","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10887,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a2"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":7118,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a3"},"answer":"FX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18218,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a4"},"answer":"B","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":31343,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65a5"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":33715,"session":"zulu","subject":"GD39M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65af"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":85951,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b0"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":13377,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b1"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":21243,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b2"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":16164,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":68914,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":12217,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":52845,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":82536,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b7"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":42860,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":7452,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65b9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":11208,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ba"},"answer":"FG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":10764,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65bb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":12936,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65bc"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6279,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65bd"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":17570,"session":"zulu","subject":"AV66J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65c7"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":61289,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65c8"},"answer":"K","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":27636,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65c9"},"answer":"F","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":29218,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ca"},"answer":"H","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":25099,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65cb"},"answer":"AIO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":126413,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65cc"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":6382,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65cd"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":6.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":45173,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ce"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":50876,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65cf"},"answer":"I","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":80413,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":15064,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d1"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":12361,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d2"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":19859,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d3"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":17492,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d4"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":8411,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65d5"},"answer":"GKX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":272069,"session":"zulu","subject":"MKTF4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65df"},"answer":"A","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","rt":28931,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e0"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","rt":33464,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e1"},"answer":"Z","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","rt":34547,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e2"},"answer":"U","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","rt":80121,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e3"},"answer":"O","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","rt":55344,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e4"},"answer":"EG","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","rt":31279,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e5"},"answer":"XO","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":3.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","rt":78073,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e6"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","rt":63626,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e7"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":0,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","rt":45420,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e8"},"answer":"E","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":10,"question":"ends","rt":14049,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65e9"},"answer":"ML","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":11,"question":"starttime","rt":10475,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ea"},"answer":"G","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":12,"question":"starts","rt":11485,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65eb"},"answer":"EF","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2.5,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":13,"question":"meets","rt":18072,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ec"},"answer":"X","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":1,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":14,"question":"endtime","rt":6522,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6180b600732570cf33cf65ed"},"answer":"KX","axis":"Orthogonal-XInside-YFull","clicks":2,"condition":"211","correct":1,"explicit":2,"impasse":1,"orth_correct":0,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","rt":18641,"session":"zulu","subject":"BHZYG"}]
